Same sir
Freshers smoke you don't bring facts you bring light and you don't tell truth
You cast roles and you pick the wrong
One for me
You build a case out of side-eyes, thumbnails and tone
You turn a rumor to a rally, put it up on a throne
Take a dozen loose fragments, stitch a monster from scraps
Then you point at your creation, like, see, I'm just stating facts
Now you bait with suggestion, let implication do flips
Got a mouth full of poison and a courtroom eclipse
Everything's a pattern when you need the crowd fed
You sell fear and a sermon with a live stream and step, step, step
creation
First comes the grand theory, then the casket's assigned, then you act like you got x-ray vision straight into my mind
And everybody's a puppet, everybody's in play, till the facts hit the room and your mystique melts away
You call paranoia wisdom, call projection a d-
How you do it right float a charge then dim the light let the audience connect the dots while you act shocked at what they got
I'm just asking question sure with a loaded wink and a poison slur. I'm just noticing a trend. Yeah, every witch hunts is that in the end
Chona has a channel. She's from the Philippines. She's really helped me get started on getting
my first 1000 subscribers, I think. You know, helped me so much. Hey, good to see you. Thank you
for coming. Good to see you. Yeah. Really awesome. Just make sure you subscribe to her channel and
go say hi to her because she's super cool and be very respectful, please. So how's everyone doing?
Um, I had a, I had a pretty good day, you know, better than
last night. Got motion. Thank you. I'm good. I'm better. I'm
better. Um, I kind of a crazy night last night. It was a
little bit, maybe I was a little bit inappropriate and
someone's, when I was on someone's panel, I was, but I got
mad.
But again, if you saw my earlier song tonight, it's like, you know, I'm gonna be trying to be moving on from some of these
Just like spider webs why green color, I don't know the color green. Oh cuz you're a member
I think cuz you're a member. He's here. You're a member. So oh
Yeah, you get a mod of course. I am I just I mod everybody all the time, you know, and then remod them and
Yeah, you're of course you get a mod, of course
Joan is great. She's she likes to dancing
In some Madonna, oh you like the green on the on the cover. Hold on. Hey Kate. How are you? Thanks for having me on tonight, Kate
You just see okay. How you great show tonight
There we go
And trackable it's midnight you'll join me great come on up you're always welcome always good to talk to you
Yeah
Thank you everybody
Midnight over there. Yeah 9 p.m. Over here. We'd like 11 trackable tone is awesome
You got the mod, right? Okay. Good. There you go. I'm skinny, but it looks good. Okay. Thank you
No, I don't have any muscle. Hey Sharon. How are you sweetheart? Good to see you
You see you. Yeah, I don't know where the starving cats. I don't have any starving cats. I got you see Lenore
No, there's them trackable. Let's welcome to the show untrackable
He man the ultimate hero idea trying to think of theme songs for everybody. Hello. Hold on one second. There you go. Hi
How are you doing very well, and I hope you are and everyone else is as well. Yeah, well good
I mean everyone else. I think it's a good day. I mean, I got a good I got a few good maps
Hey Nick nicks here Nick, of course, you know, he was Wendy a few days ago then today. He did his tire
His tire exercise where he has this tractor tire and he you know flips it over about a hundred times
or more. So what do you do for exercise? I'm untrackable.
You have a pretty fit body. I can say so myself.
He's a little silver fox guys, silver fox right here.
No, I am not fit anymore.
I don't know. It looks like you got that chest.
You got that chest, you know, that every man wants, you know,
Well, you know, I've been thinking about this is like
You spend so much time
Building something up right
But how long does it take to break it down?
when you
Don't you don't maintain well just takes me take maintenance, but once you get the once you get it built up
You know, it just takes a little maintenance. It doesn't the hard part of the guess is building it up, right?
Yeah, I think I made it through the hard part
Good
But when you do nothing in fact you do negative I smoke I drink
Yeah, I do so much so much that is not good for me
How long does it take before this body just gives up?
Well, you know, the body actually is, in my just in my opinion, I think the body is pretty resilient.
For example, like, you know, I have pretty good abs and I don't really do very much, you know.
But there's genetics involved, there's, you know.
You know, just just move it. You know, there's also something called harm reduction because we do harm ourselves in so many ways
We we do these, you know, these bad habits of smoking and the drinking and the and some people, you know
Different drugs and different, you know being lazy. There's a million
There's there's also things we can do to counteract that and at least not make the the damage so bad, right?
And so it's always important to make sure
Or at least always getting up maybe going outside
every day at least like a little bit and
Taking a walk, you know, just just that's just doing something a little bit besides
You know, it's like every little bit helps, you know, and it's like I think that the good we do
Can outweigh the bad, you know, that's just my my thoughts on it, but yeah
I mean, I mean for for instance if you build a sandcastle
Yeah, it's it's a beautiful
Sandcastle, but a couple of waves sandcastles gone, right
But then again, it's just made of sand if you're to build a you know put a little you know concrete or a
little you know stone stone foundation and you can fortify it and
You know because castles not gonna last long any jerk's gonna come by and stomp on it when they can you know and your beautiful work is done
So it's like you know we can also
Fortify our creations that that's the story of the three pigs. It's like
Right, you know how how sad a straw
And and then
When they built their house out of bricks, you know the the wolf
Had no competition. We'll just hurt some stuff. Oh, I like your shirt. We haven't done our guests on will come
Is anthrax, this is my e-boo
He's my e-boo so that's only for fifty dollar fifty dollars. That's too much. Oh my gosh, you got ripped off. I'm so sorry
Yeah, I did get ripped off. What a fucker
Hey meet untrackable. I don't know if you've met untrackable and trackable is a great guy. This is my this is Squidward. He's my Ibu
So one boy
Is prairie page the police prairie page, you know, she's uh
You know, she does she does get she gave good she gave good advice from her heart. I think that maybe
She was she wasn't quite didn't quite know a hundred percent of
What was going like going on maybe with me and stuff and maybe
Um, we could have elaborate in that conversation, but you know, she was from her heart and I appreciate her and you know
She's been with the show since the beginning. She never kind of like turned on me like a lot of people have and I love page and I think like
You know, I hope I helped her too
I think she came in a difficult time in her life and I hope I helped her too
You know, but she's always going to be welcome here and you know no matter what
You know and basically I'm not gonna really gonna turn many people away and also, you know
Some people have done me kind of wrong, but my door's still open for them too because I'll always if I always accept a genuine apology
I don't really even expect an apology really
You know because I probably owe apologies to you know, and I'm not perfect, right? I make mistakes and
sometimes
You know things happen, but you know, I love page and
I think page first staying by me, you know, no matter what
So how are we doing? Yeah, so this is like yeah, so this is he I don't let you know Chris K
But I think I was friends with Chris K, but he's long time ago, bro
Squidward is, you know, he's from Granola Bars, yes.
Squidward is in Vegas, he knows Chris K,
I don't know if you know Chris, oh yeah,
he did this a long time ago, he knew him.
But yeah, Squidward's a good guy.
You're not too drunk tonight, so that's good.
Yeah, I'm not on Granola, no more.
That sure makes me insane.
The Granola?
The other Granola.
I've never heard anybody say that, but.
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Well, you know
Vegas is a place where that's like if you go to if you go in a casino at any time you go at three in the morning
They had the same lighting
24 hours a day. I mean, it's like it's really rich of strength on the ship
Recharge well, yeah, let's say mentally disabled strength, but no, um, yeah
Oxygen well, but say how to untrackable and trackable. I think he's a good maybe role model
I don't know you might you might disagree, but I think he's like this is he's a very stand-up guy. He's a very
You know, you can see he's a silver fox, right? But um, you know, he's he is he always has good advice. He always is
measured and calm and
I don't recommend doing drugs. This is just a disclaimer. Okay. Um, everyone's different reacts differently to drugs or alcohol
Right. I mean, I don't I don't recommend any of this behavior. Yeah
right
And hey, we all have our wild, our wild times.
We can sew our, they call it sewing our oats.
And sometimes when we're younger,
we're experimenting with different things.
And I know some people,
sometimes we see people around us,
you know, become succumb to the real negative sides of things.
I think, I think pretty much,
we're a lot of survivors here.
You know, I think there's a lot of survivors here.
Maybe there's some, some outcasts, maybe there's some.
I got a job tomorrow.
Good.
Got gas money.
I got all this shit.
Oh, good.
I had a little bit of extra cash this week
because my YouTube did pay this month.
I didn't know if it would, but it paid a couple of days
after that.
It usually does, but hey, I'm thankful that I'm
able to have a little extra.
I'm thankful to be alive to be breathing.
Right and think about yeah, and we are and it's like especially because I don't know if you heard untrackable
But I have a friend that he was a streamer
And a great guy and I was just on a show so much recently and then just a couple weeks ago
He was on a stream and then he went oh, I got to run to the gas station
He was shot three times in his chest at the gas yeah, and he was
He had two he had two two daughters and stuff, but it's like it's so
Coral for the poor for the dead homie
And it's I mean it's so sad I don't remember that
Yeah, it's sad. I mean, it's so sad. I mean, it's like and there's but there's a reason you know things happen sometimes
But it's like also I mean there's a reason that he's he was streaming like almost 24-7 recently
and just there and
Had like a little bit of a glow to him and stuff like that and
Almost like, you know, I don't know and it's like I think what what what if I had
saw him streaming that night that night it happened I saw his stream on and it
was he had a kind of a negative title like he's like oh everyone I'm subscribed
to me everyone's fake blah blah and I was always in a bad mood I'll just not
not go over there but you know
What if I had gone the night and the five minutes, you know, the five minutes difference and that person wouldn't have been at the gas
It's something like that or maybe that person was just waiting at the gas station just from the guy
You know, if we just don't know if we can't there's so many things we can't control in this life, right?
Yeah, I think just having a faith that I think I want revenge, but like I can't do nothing about it
I mean, well, yeah, I don't know
I mean they got my homie like before
and it's like, and we're, but is there anybody here that hasn't had hasn't lost somebody like it's like that's what happens in this world. We lost a lot of your friends, you lost a lot of your friends, that's fine, we're all good, we're still alive, we're still alive, and it's like, you know, and it's like, but it really, uh,
So you want me to show his push-ups one-handed who does one-handed push-ups and trackable you're saying he doesn't wait
Doesn't one-handed put I don't know if he's in the mood to do that
But you know he does always impressed me with his his fitness. I think he's a little hard on himself thinking that
He's he's just falling apart. I think he's still looking good to me
I remember also when he was on the show one night me
He was like, hey, I'm going to start shaping my beard for Danny.
Oh, yeah.
Things haven't been the same since you lost someone, Jamie.
Yeah, so yeah, we can say a prayer for Danny.
I mean, Danny was just a good guy.
I can tell good guys because good guys will be like.
They'll be nice to me like when you wouldn't maybe expect them to be like you wouldn't maybe think that they're from a different culture or different
You know mindset, but he's always he's always kind to me
Did I see the video which which one Jamie he does one hand of push-ups in the video?
Yeah, maybe I look for can you can you can you post it Jamie? I'll watch it if you can
Post it and oh aliens back. Hey alien. How are you? Alien was in the chat today. Love in the kitties
I look at a little kitty love fest today. I had Lenore just kissing
Lola was a
Cuddling up here. You can see the kitty cats, you know, where's where's Lola. Oh, it's hard to see
I'm gonna take off my background real quick. I see some kitty cats guys here. You see
I'd do this remove the background. There we go
Yeah, you can see
Hard to see them. Here's Lola right there. She's in the back
You can kind of see her peeking out and there's Lenore see me on top of the
Oh the blanket. Trixie's over
Over in the kitchen right there. You can see I'm kind of laying down on the little cushion
Trixie Trixie
And I don't see Rudy, but yeah, I do have four cats and today again people were like oh
You had nine cats and now you have four like what happened to all your five cats well
I'll tell you again. I had it. Sorry. Lola had a litter of kittens of five kittens and
Most of the kittens except for tricks, you know
assimilated into the neighborhood.
Thank you, Jamie.
Yeah, and so, I mean, would people be happy
if I had nine cats and stuff?
And why is it their business?
I don't know, but it's just constantly being attacked
for my cats because that's where it hurts, you know?
Because my cats are my little angels,
my little beloved, you know?
And so, but the fact that people will try
to hit you where it hurts.
is kind of sad to me, right?
It's like, it happens to other people that have kids.
It happens to people that have, you know,
it's like on this, I mean, when you get trolled,
they're gonna troll your most precious things
you hold most dear sometimes.
And that's something we have to also fortify against, right?
Just like that sandcastle.
We can fortify against these trolls
and knowing that they're just saying things to upset us
and to get us out of our element.
Right and oh, you got a cock. You have a big cock hat
Look at that smile he does have a smile
Mexicans have cock hats. I know it's called it's called Gayo, right? Gayo?
Gayos, yeah
I used to know the guy person named Cox. Yeah, cuz what talks?
Well, you got big talks
We're in the big cock club here, but we're talking about chickens, right?
Yeah
Well, you wouldn't expect any less from my boyfriend, right? Well, well, I don't know if you were officially yet, right?
But uh, that is funny as hell. Okay. He's cute and he's this I think he's straight
He's mostly straight. He's like I think he's like 90% straight the 10%
By curious side of him. That's all mine
Man I'll leave this straight side alone. Maybe are you are you interested in like you know getting married some day to a woman and stuff?
Squid
Not really. I mean like maybe
Maybe not this plan. I really care. Okay. Well
Are you interested in marrying me?
Okay
Okay, well we can think about we can talk about it later. We'll talk about that later
Yeah
Let's marry each other and piss everyone off. We would we would that would be fucking funny as hell
That's why that's why I really
Yeah, yeah, make make sure somebody has insurance and if somebody has an inheritance
You know make a deal, but you're gonna spend time together
You you have to make it work
and
Making it work is
You know
Even when even even when there is so much easiness in love
Um, you know, time makes things hard and then, and then the questions, you don't know the
questions until they are asked.
You understand what I'm saying?
Right.
Um, Jamie just sent me this quick video.
It's a short of my friend Danny.
The one who just passed away. He's doing one-handed push-ups. If you're interested in having a quick one-handed push-ups
Yeah, some of them, right? I want to go that tire shit with the other Squidward
The others there's another oh the other
I'm gonna lose weight
You need to well Nick Nick Johnson. He's here. I think he's under burning joint. He can help fucking. I'm a fat Mexican
Okay, okay
I'm sure
Your poncho. You're are you Mexican?
I
Can barely do a push-up let alone
Cheeks
Well, there's Danny's doing I think one-handed push-ups. It says one-handed push-ups is a big lighter
Let's have a look. This is gonna be
You know a nice little memory. He has some great. He has a great clips. We're here. You're like
Untrackable, but it's gonna be a red beard
Well
When I when I grow my beard they call me a red bush
red bush
There's not many many Mexicans with the orange hair, but
to be able to
a little better
if you don't like the way you look
then don't do it
or even just shave it all off, I'll look younger
if that's your concern
I look like different, like 20 years old
Okay, let's have a look at this is the Danny stranger clip. Oh, he's doing your watch this real quick
He's doing he's doing one-handed push-ups. He looks like he has a doggy. Oh, yeah
There's there's on burning joint by the way. He says 100% he'll help you out, but this is Danny
Doing one-handed push-ups with a big lighter. This is called the one the impossible one-handed push-up on a big
Okay, and I mean sure I got it pulled up for us. Okay. Share this. Okay
Here he is
Just have a nice memories of
Our friend Danny before present. Okay, hold my it's not coming up remove other mediums. Okay. I don't this one
Okay, got it. Okay. Got it. Here's Danny doing the one-handed push-up
Impossible one-handed push-up. Let's see
One-handed push-up on a big lighter
I don't remember the dog he has coming over. Look at this dog. Look at the dog coming right over
Let's fucking go
There you go, I'm pretty crazy, right?
Let's watch one more time
I don't know. Look at the dog. I just love the dogs. They're like, they come right under. Yeah. Yeah
Let's fucking go you tell that dog loves him too that that's pretty
You look like you're losing weight your neck is like your neck looks like a nice neck to massage
I'd like to like, you know, just like grab that
Looks a little little bit thick. I like it
And you just talked about we just talked about like facial hair
Yeah, stop stop talking about what you can do and just do something
Right. So go grow the mullet grow the beard
Just do something
Just do it like Nike says, you know, just do it. Whatever you want to do it not in the weird Nike wave
We know there's some negative don't have acid
Don't play for your failure. Just fucking do it
Wrong to say is like hey
The moment you mention
I came or I wish I could or something like that it's like just fucking do it
if you say you just do it I'm not doing that again because my voice is like you
can do something just do it if you can and you're telling yourself that you
can't and so you know it's like if you say you can I'm then able to like get
Well, I'm good though
Well, and they were doing that show you and this is the kind of younger guy on track
Well, I'm 45 on track. Well, I think it's probably around my age and then we're talking to like this guys
He's a young spring a spring guy. Oh or poyo a snorted mess
In Minecraft in Minecraft calm down
Whoa
Yeah, we had we sometimes some of the things are a little bit uh
Little bit shocking that comes out of people's mouth, but uh
It's okay
People like just lying
People like do all that shit. They're hypocrites. So who cares? I think everyone's done every that everyone's done something
That's somebody else would probably be shocked about you know, and it's like that's just part of part of being human is like
Sometimes walking into things
ignorant blind and sometimes
You know on purpose and stuff, but that's it. That's all another thing. I think about it. It was judgment
It's very easy to judge other people
But are we them? Are we have we been through their experiences that we come come to where they have come?
Because they're like pussies
Well, they just lie lie lie lie about you
That that's where that's where another thing comes into factor is
Even when somebody says hey, I'm gonna put my effort into this and they fail
The there's gonna a lot of be a lot of people that say oh
You said you said you said and you failed
But if you're still here
then you have the opportunity to
change course or
try again or
You know, however, it winds up being
But if you actually went through with what you said you were gonna go through with
Well, you know failure is an option
Trying again is an option.
Changing course and learning from your failures is an option.
And we're still here too. Like, think about this.
Yeah, I mean, we're still here to try.
People have done worse. People have done worse things.
Right, and it's like really the people that you really do the worst things
Maybe they should be like, you know locked up like a lot of people are yeah
You think we do have a good legal system that will take care of these things
We like to like do this public this public trial and I don't want to send death threats no more cuz like
If you send death threats, you better fucking mean it motherfuckers. Yeah, we don't want to do that because first of all
We don't read most of the time. We won't mean it. We will say
Every mother fucker that sends death fucking threats to my family people. I love
But you better fucking come to my place motherfuckers, you're not gonna see
Most people that will say that except about our especially on the internet, you know people to say
Say that shit on the street
Yeah, most people wouldn't say to our fate. That's the thing about trolls. Is that you're fucking asked what?
By the way, I do want to thank vegan Patriot like and I don't know if vegan Patriot is listening or anything
but vegan Patriot did
Give some me some great advice last night on several a couple of my posts and she's a scorpio bushy
Yeah, I think she's okay. I think she's a really good person and
Well, I wouldn't say anything negative because it's like like when I was having a kind of like outburst and my own thing
She came a fucking drunk. It's okay. It's okay. Hey
I used to be a pretty bad drunk. I'm still like, you know, and I still drink but I try to
I try to just pace myself a little bit more, right?
It's like, especially, I have a responsibility
on the show to keep the show safe,
to keep the show, you know, on.
You know, my show's been taken down four times
on this channel, on a monetized channel, by the way.
It's been taken down four times.
All four times, I got it brought back up.
And so, you know, nothing's really impossible,
even though the third time, pretty impossible.
It was a pretty impossible situation.
There's a miracle and so sometimes miracles will happen. I'd say have a have a have a relationship with this higher power to like really
Pray they all these motherfuckers that are talking hella shit. Thank you at Jamie
They got skeletons in your goddamn closet. They know what they did
If it's the last
I found motherfuckers. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, and that's the
You know, that's the number one like
Accusation and stuff people will say that they're projecting what they are, right? Right. Well, it's like and it's like really it's like
If you ever do people were to do something like that they should be you know very much kept away from clean
I'm pure. I'm clean. Well. Yeah. Hey, we have another video of Danny
This is this time he's doing doing a push-up on a deodorant stick. Is anyone interested in seeing this?
I definitely am so this is old spice. Okay, this guy's he's gonna do an old spice deodorant push-up
So let's have a look at this one
Everybody let's have a look at the old one-handed push-up on a deodorant. I think this was his on the way push up
On a deodorant. Yeah, and I'm gonna show here. We go. I'm gonna share it here
You go. I mean just remove this one and add this one. Okay, and
Thank you for getting you guys for like, you know and Danny's a really cool guy
There we go. I mean is it up there yet? Yeah, hold on. Do you see it? Oh, no, you don't see it. Here we go
There he is. Okay. Let's have a look at this
a one-handed push-up on deodorant.
See what I can do.
Oh.
Ooh.
You got it.
Oh, here.
Ooh, I'm shaking with a wobbly there.
I thought I was going to eat shit.
Can you do that?
I don't know. I don't know.
You feel it you feel like electricity because you're in the middle of it right now, but yeah, there's those electricity passing
Passing through. I'm sorry if it's a little bit gay energy, but no, no. No, I'm just
Mine his gay energy. It's not yours. It's our game and but every time
People can't take a gay joke for once like that's really like
Who's the fucking gay joke, dude?
You know, Mexicans talk gay so much
Like they talk gay jokes all the time, dude. Yeah, I mean it's like busting balls
Sometimes it's not a joke because I am gay, but you know, yeah
I think these guys are cool
You know just to put up with me like to be on this show sometimes you will people will say oh, this is that grateful
Thank you for your comment. Don't let the drama effect. You just Spanish. I heard like these military members like from the Marina
The marines. Yeah, we're in us. Why do I need a woman if I if I got you precious?
Preciosos
Yeah, and it's like and then it's like it's all a joke until they have 20 beers now because they literally defend themselves
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, and it's like but then it's like, you know
Hey, what's up clumsy? How are you? Good to see you clumsy being gang is here clumsy
You better not fucking talk shit nigger
It's hard for me to watch videos Jamie it is hard for me to watch his videos just because he's gone and stuff
And it's clumsy all he does is complain and bitch and complain about everybody
Come up here motherfucker
Okay, we're talking nice. We're talking nice right here. We're having a good time. I
Had
I have my uh, I'm gonna put my my link up again. If anyone's welcome to join it. We got
The great uncrackable
Or is over here. Oh, no, she's a source for the source
I thought she was a heavy set woman, but she's not she's like kind of a skinny goth chick
And uh, he has no proof. He says bunch of bullshit. It doesn't fuck send the clips then send the clips what I said then plus
If not, it's over. Don't even mention my mother fucking me
Bitch. Oh, yeah, and there's uh, we have our friend. I am. We're all good now. We're all homies right here
We are homies. This is I next if you want to come up tonight
I don't know if it's the right night for you to come up if you always all scared of you want to come up
Yeah, we want beef and got warm on mother fucker. Yeah. Well, let's not have a war. Hey, how about like let's make love not war
Yeah, let's make love so about the violence stop talking shit about people. Yeah
It's all good so good so I was on I was on careless Kate's earlier and I next came up and and you know
I next is also a great person, you know
Wow, I mean it's like
I keep I keep I don't know why I keep I'm going back to like, you know, be this you know
Like it's not funny when people threaten like innocent people innocent families
Well, that's not right. You know, it is that's literally disrespectful as fuck. Yeah, we know we touch me touch me
Okay
No
I don't know why I keep going to betas and it's like I keep thinking like you know
It isn't sanity because I keep thinking that it's gonna be a different outcome. It's always pretty much the same outcome
I go up there. We talked for a few minutes. It's good then man
Then on comes Sam man
Other people and stuff and I think always goes wrong
My willing to like keep working on the relationship if there's a glimmer of hope like a little like maybe
We can get somewhere somewhere to like some kind of understanding or some kind of like it's no bro
I'll really knock a motherfucker out
Okay
Okay, okay, don't fight with the chat stuff. I mean you're okay
Hey, honey. Mm-hmm. Calm down. Okay. I'll come down. Okay
Thank you. Oh, man. Oh goodness gracious. I mean, I love this guy. I love I love this guy. Um, but
You know, and he's a teddy bear. He really is a teddy bear, but you know a teddy bear
They can turn into like a grizzly bear sometime they can go back to the natural
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I know and I know
I'm just a little drunk, you know
I'm a little drunk too. I just chugged a hurricane punch. I have two I have two lemonade
And so hey sloppy Joe
Good to see you. There's an army here. Yeah, there's an army here. I need I mean the other night it was pretty crazy
Yeah, but my life was threatened the other night because of you know Alex was going Alex McQueen was going a little bit wild and stuff
Yeah, and I don't know you
Everybody I can't show this meme earlier
I know there's a there's a there's a when did the weird beef start with beat up
It started I think with Arthur saying something terrible. I think our
You know, you know in the military people could stay awake for a month straight
You think women can handle that?
It's not a good idea to stay awake for like a month straight plus. You think women can handle that?
If they're a good with their badass woman, yes, but like most women cannot handle that shit
I do I do want to show you this this meme that was made by you know
Constantly fucking fighting dude. This woman that is not a big fan of mine
But we actually met in person had a great dinner
She was like she had more terror readings for me than I think ever you know anybody else and we were great friends
And for no reason really for no reason she turned on me like you know people said like she turned on other people
Um, it's hurtful. Why don't they send them to the war? Hold on. Did they take each other?
Did she take the meme down? Hold on. There's a meme that she put up. Oh, here is that?
Oh, there's one with, I don't know, clumsy. Have you seen your meme that she made? She made a meme with clumsy and good times?
I'll show you guys these a couple memes that she made. This is a clumsy on good times channel. I just need to change the
Format. You know who clumsy is, right? Um, I'm trackable
Clumsy is the you know, he's an Hispanic man. He's in the bean game. Okay here
Okay, okay, okay, I know it's bad. Well, you can't have no fucking wardrobe. It's okay. Okay, but we're good though
We're good though. Well, this is the clumsy meme
Yeah
It's his imagine what it looks like it's full. He's such a clown. So I don't know
Clumsy aid. He's a he's imagined with certain hermets. That's why it looks like a real life
But the podcast host he inspired to start desktop streaming. Well, I don't know why is he eating fried chicken and watermelon and I guess
Who's that is that good times? Yeah, that's good times for life
Yeah, and then there's clumsy is the cool
These people have no lives like they literally live off the government our taxes are ebt not no they get ebt
Yeah, okay. There are a drain on the fucking economy, bro. Well, it doesn't work doesn't
Money, I think she's all bad
They've had a certain amount of money aside for you. Now. This is a strange one
I mentioned this on beat is and then Kate showed it. So this is like I don't know if these are very
Metta kind of kind of means I mean, I'm in this one. I'm Tommy James is in this one and you know, Crystal Anne
We know she made an appearance in this one
So I'm just gonna show you this so if anyone can explain it to me
I well, I guess it's because she says, you know, I worship some kind of some kind of
Horrible demon that does the worst things, but let me see. I'll show you this here
Imagine like remember the lesson that someone said I'm clumsy from the Mexican cartel. I
Remember yeah, you remember what is this one mean can you explain?
That's weird I don't know what that is
Well, I think it's a some kind of daycare center without Tommy James and Chris Land are babies
I'm so I'm some kind of water. I don't support that
No, I don't support this either. I was on a monster. It says Tommy James says it's just hiding my receding baldness and Chris Land
It says I was that I'm ashamed. What does this mean? I don't know. That's why I'm asking if anyone know what it means
Well, that's Tommy James and Chris Solana's baby and it says imagine if Aaron Carter house
Sorry, he would house how bad Aaron Carter feels
Okay, take it off
Don't like that one. Okay. Well, I look weird. Well, it's because of Lilith. I think because of Lilith
Who is actually like a god?
Thank you. Tell me the truth. What was that?
That was Alexandra Bayer's interpretation. Those are two little kids. What was that?
That's Tommy James and Crystal Anne. Tell me the truth. What the fuck did I just see?
That was not a real picture. That was a meme someone made. Okay. Okay. That was not me. I believe you
Bronzeberg kick you that's here for $50 to come back. I know well, you know
I'm a ghost, they're going to be asking for money because they're so jealous that ghosts
is a donated to me, like you know, be to ask them for 20 bucks to go on.
Now, Bronzeberg is asking for $50, let's just see what's happening here.
You look at this fucking
Don't say that
He literally just said no no no no come up. Okay, he literally just said it was
He said maggot he said those he did not say that those if you're such a badass gangster
Can the fuck up?
Are you a female?
No, no probably some like one. Okay. I don't like one anything else
Anything else you want to say motherfucker? I didn't say anything. I just asked you what did you just say them?
work out
You're fucking retard it. Would you like me to say the water party? Okay, so we've got a
Fighting no fighting. I know I don't know the fuck comes up like this guy you shut the fuck on the fuck
You're down to angry Squidward. Go tell me that's where you're literally. Yeah, bitch
That's what happens dumb dumb, you know fuck with me
Yeah, let's not get let's not get angry. So I'll leave back in five minutes exactly. Okay, just calm down. Take a breather
You want to hear some bullshit site? What happened? I was just on another panel
someone paid 25 dollars to fucking
$25 for the whole night
to kick you up for the night
Yeah, they said if you want to come back. I was like, yeah, I got 20. Obviously, you know, I don't give a fuck
I was like
Yeah, he wants double. Yeah. Well, that's like because of like, you know
The 25 is like to make it even and then the 25 is to come back 26 beats 20
I don't give a fuck how you look at 26 beats 25. Well, I don't know
I mean they say I wouldn't be I wouldn't be sending him double. You fucking idiot. You're retard. You dumbass
No, it's like Brunsberg is a is I actually I called him a slave the other night. Oh, were you watching it?
It's not to be raised. I wasn't watching but I called him a slave not because I'm trying to be racial
But because he said you dox miss beta
I'm slave to the money
He has no idea what you're talking about just laying and stuff like that. I don't know why it's miss beta
I mean but I mean this is not colonial times and do I have
Should I give not should but do I have enough obviously have enough money obviously it's what I do
But why would I do that like that's just respectful as fuck?
Hey, you know what you want to make him mad if you're doing you know what I
But here's the things like this is what I used to do to make them mad. I used to pay
So like kick people off, you know, I did ever right after that
I literally pay to have literally within 60 seconds. I'd pay to have them right back on
Well, I know well you can do that
Don't play with me don't play with bronze and retard it
Do you want to and it you know buy yourself a vest here, and then you can never be kicked off?
And it will look good on you and
Where we know that's what I'm gonna say and that's fucking retard it like
$25 is a cheap price that should only be like 20 minutes you 25 hours for though
I don't even know what the whole night means.
What if you don't go live for four days?
I know, oh my gosh, I mean, who knows, who knows.
But I wanna show you some of what's been said.
Here, I'm gonna let this guy back on.
You better calm down, Squid, okay?
I'm gonna show you-
Come the fuck down, Plankton.
And shut the fuck up when you talk to me.
You guys wanna hear some of like-
Why did you just fucking tell me, motherfucker?
I'm not gonna mention this.
Fuck up, please.
Everyone calm down.
All right, you talk.
Look at one of us
Motherfuckin can he fucking talk shit. No, no, no fucking team. Go ahead
You fucking camera bitch
Okay, what the fuck are you to talk to me like that son of a bitch?
Do it for you my nigga
Okay, cool. It's his piano. He's running anything else for me though. Yeah, whatever. Let's let's see what he has to say
I don't give a fucking on me. Okay
Why don't you sit there and shut the fuck up then?
Let me see. Well, okay. I want you to know why you're the ghost has no motion
I mean
What is this
Do you understand that Alexander mayors is crazy
And today I would like to go over what the artificial intelligence or AI has to say in
regards to the fraud within these streaming communities who is actively and aggressively
promoting demon worship in the IRL communities, a demon known as Lilith specifically.
As of today, this particular fraud has gone as far as to say that this particular demon
is a goddess. That is not true. A simple google search will reveal to all of you that for thousands
of years, Jewish mysticism has labeled the demon known as Lilith as being very detrimental to people
All walks of faith. It's not something to be played with. It's something to be taken seriously
It's not a joke and
In no way, shape or form, regardless of your belief system,
should you put any credibility
into this demon known as Lilith,
you should not worship it.
It will do nothing but bring negative energy
into your life.
And anyone promoting this particular demon
without a doubt is evil
because this particular demon is known to harm babies,
children why in the world would anyone try to deify any sort of energy known to
harm babies and children I don't know the answer to that question but let's just
start with exact
What happened?
What she just said
She asked the add very leading
So if she's saying all this shit about harming children whatever ball blah blah, but then she has a right
To fuck with motherfuckers like us
What a hypocrite
You know what we're gonna do you know
Nothing we're ain't gonna do shit
We're all good
What is this
Talking about me psyche
Where's this listen who is that is that a demon?
Clips I just covering with my own picture
Who is it?
Lily Lily. Yeah, Lily. What the fuck is Lillis?
Chris, what the fuck is Lily?
Whoa, what?
Are you good?
My bad, I'm carried away. We're trying to get fucked up like this bro. It's just like I mean
I'm just fucked up
But I'm still gonna work tomorrow good good
Most of the people they haven't worked one day of their life
Like the C word clumsy. You can't even hear it. Okay. It's fine. I put up something else. Okay, never mind
Why am I beefing with everybody? Why? I don't know. I don't know. Whoa
Everyone's mad. Okay. Well, everyone's not I mean, she's actually you think I have time to like stock cringisaurus
I don't even know who the fuck that is. She's she's a little bit of a crazy golf chick. I mean, she is gonna
You know, I don't give a fuck do whatever you want do witchcraft. Well, I don't mean it's like I know it's craft but I've
use a watch bitch
Well, maybe I mean, it's like I mean I call a bitch craft some of the time it's craft
Yeah, I mean there's a little bitch craft
bitch craft it's like
In Minecraft bitchcraft
Oh
Clumsy coming up and I'm coming up clumsy come up. Well, clumsy, you know now. She's
From the homie. He's homie. He's she turned against you to clumsy because now there's an episode called
Mexican cartels and demon worshipers and she says that I am
Being hired by the Mexican mafia
To do which witchcraft for them, but she says a bunch of lies bunch of lies. They're gonna get by Delta Force anyway
But what about Delta Force? What are they gonna do to me?
Not you, but everyone
There's no fucking proof. What what is the proof?
She hasn't she's asked the AI about it with very leading questions
I know I will I know I know I don't think you'll be on the show. I'm sorry. I'm sorry if that chased you away
I'm sorry
Everything is gonna come in our favor because I think so. Yeah, I know isn't you I'm sorry, you know why why what's up?
Because all these motherfuckers do is lie
I know and the truth comes to light it will it will welcome to light pretty soon
Good, it's already happening. Yeah, I hope it does so like more cocksuckers
I want everything to come to life. I want the dream. Yes, sir
Yeah, like anybody that is gonna make accusations. I better have some proof
I better have some very big proof and without some proof clumsy never has proof about shit
He's the old you said this you said that this is motherfucking didn't stop texting me. Leave me the fuck alone
You're texting my boyfriend clumsy. What a pussy ass
Go lose weight you titty fucker. Oh my god. Yeah, please take these clumsy too
Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Are there milk in them?
Let's see. How well are the heroin you did?
You don't have teeth. I can't play them.
I can't play them. They're gonna be emptied away.
I played a big, I played a big bird song and then my channel got taken. I got a strike for playing.
I'm a blooper, but I can sing it to you.
I'm a bluebird so all you better back the fuck off of me there. Oh Peter South. Are you Peter North's younger brother?
Peter South, okay?
That of a rainbow I can follow
You know, you know Big Bird. I love it. Oh, we have a guest. Let's welcome clumsy bean gang to the show. Hey
Bamba la la la la Bamba
There we go. Oh, now he wants a cam off. Uh-oh. Yeah. What up, Pusty boy?
What up, McWampa? Hey, why do you have me blocked, bro, where I can't show people the messages now?
You blocked me, you stupid fuck. Yeah, cuz you kept on texting me like a female, my nigga. You too. Okay, okay.
She's fine. No, but they put this on Sunday
I told you I don't care about
Bro
Disappearing message
Back you guys have it up. I don't know you bro. I don't
I don't care
Fuck you
I ain't your homie either my nigga. That's why I block your dumb ass. You're fucking like suck my dig and all that shit
Yeah, he do his talk shit about everybody
Who the fuck is that anyway
Why you keep on bringing up her name and killing who she is?
Because you motherfuckers are accusing me of doing something to her.
She's the one that keeps telling me to kill yourself.
Kill yourself, Squidward.
Unalike yourself. Unalike.
Talk about she kills herself.
Oh, but you don't know her though, right?
I don't know who the fuck that is. I don't even know her first name.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay.
Here's your damn shit to me.
Bro.
Why are you threatening her because she didn't want nothing to do with you?
I don't know because she started it, bitch.
She's married!
She started it!
We're gonna take the trails later!
She told you she's married!
We got...
I don't give a fuck about her!
She's married!
She didn't want nothing to do with you!
I have a girlfriend!
Have a girlfriend!
Of course you do.
She's ugly.
She's disgusting.
But yeah, you're on the internet.
She smells like poop.
You're on the internet with a man.
Trying to give up your booty.
You're the one that's fucking talking.
Matches by your uncle.
You have no life.
You can eat the teeth from the government.
Thank you.
I'm
Leaching you're a pinchy salvatrucha putta
You got a girlfriend right, but yeah, you're trying to give up your fucking asshole to psyche
Who cares you're the one that fucking porn bombs
You try to let your force of fire
Everyone that porn bombs is a fucking weird
Oh show your face then
I'm still like over here in mature
Shut up nigga. You gotta be a grown man. Shut up man. You live with momma, momma and daddy.
You have no life, fuck boy.
Have a life. Hey, bro, my mom and dad. I don't know what to do. They're trying to kick me out
I drink too much. I told my check the fuck up nigga. I don't do her and like you you got hepatitis C bitch
Oh, well, you got no teeth. What happened to your teeth? Do you smoke crack?
So your teeth show your front teeth
Show me your fucking gun bitch
What gives a fuck
It's
Viewers and you because it's a dick
They're loading my ass
Amazing
Little turkey neck
That sucked so much jizz down it.
I will say that song is really nasty.
The jizz is drying out your neck, bitch.
The jizz is drying out your neck.
It looks fucking worn out and dried out, buddy.
It's not hydrating you.
It's crispy. It's crispy.
Fuck it, disgusted.
You drank cold.
Look at this new.
I have more viewers than you.
Like it.
Yeah, that's one of the cool things I've been playing.
Okay, well, okay, I'm gonna let them back. I don't want to bite any more pages here and I don't want you to bite
Yeah, what is even happening anymore? Like what are what is wrong with these bitches?
That was cringe the source that was cringe the source that bitch is insane dude. Did you just see her?
What the fuck was she talking about my nigga signal for it was me
Yeah, okay. Let's leave her. I mean, there's a numbered witches. He just bit you
And it goes weird. I know it's a little crazy. I yeah, thank you. Thank you for being here ring
I mean, it's been a little crazy lately. I mean, I do. Oh apologies and stuff. Yeah
You know, I know you're at the popo, but I want I don't want to you should have here where they're arguing
So you tell him bronze for how much you spent and why I should join
well
You can tell you can tell how much I mean it's really none of his business and stuff like that and you know
Why are you kissing his ass it goes? I mean, it's like really it's like, you know, we want to
spread things around to the right people and stuff.
I don't know.
I'm gonna try to talk to Clumsy for a minute
because I don't want you, this guy,
what's happened here, it's just been madness.
Yeah, I already said what I said, it's like Ian,
you don't have to worry about that no more, so.
They're bullying ghosts over there, okay?
They're bullying ghosts in his jet.
I know they would do that.
Okay, I'm gonna let him back.
Okay, but you better, I don't want you to fight with him, okay?
No, I'm gonna say that too, I'm gonna say no.
Don't fight, I'm gonna be between you guys here.
No fighting, please.
Calm down. Hey, honey bun. No fighting with clumsy, please. Okay
I'm just gonna look dead in the ice
Okay, just look at it. Give him the mad dog even mad dog him and stuff, you know
Does look good on a horse as like like a man, you know, that's true, bro. Yeah, he sucks dick from the government
Okay, well, let's not I'm coming down to calm down
I have a boyfriend finally and then that he's very hard to wrangle in sometimes
right
Boat thing the boot thing my boo
Yes, some Paco eyes, which is means he probably is a psychopath. Okay. He is a Scorpio, right?
You're Scorpio. Look at his eyes. Look at that. Look. Look. He's giving. Oh
What's the word on the block?
Uh, Psyche, what's going on?
I mean, I did go on a show last night,
and maybe I said the N-word a little too many times.
The police did come, and not in a good way.
You know, they just came through the door.
But actually, they're perfectly nice.
I don't know. I mean, it was, yeah.
Whew. And I got a boyfriend.
I mean, he's my boyfriend. I don't know.
He's never had a boyfriend before, so it's new for him.
But the last thing you're gonna see comes in. Oh my gosh, he's scaring me
This is the last thing you're gonna see when you see me bitch leave me the fuck
I don't want to kick you out. I don't I don't hear nothing bro. Okay good
right clumsy it was fun the other night though wasn't a fun like what it was like two to six in the morning and it was like
Um, hey, we're chilling. Yeah, I enjoyed it. We're just chilling. Okay with Chris K
Then Sam and came up and like the war dog guy came up
I do want to show you like guys, I finally am finished with my website, you know
I mean keep talking about this, but yeah
If you want to go if you want to search every single episode if you want to look at every I have every transcript of every show
Listed and things like that. Like it's like everything is there. I've never seen anything like this
It's called cult codex dot me and it's like you can go here and I bet clumsy will be on it like we see if he's on it
Let me see
So this is like the this is the codex and I can show you how it looks.
So this is called the living archive of my show.
Okay. It's pretty very, very detailed.
Oh, he left. Okay. Okay. Well, anyway, so we have a cult of psyche right there.
Okay. And then let's see if you have clumsy. It says people.
Right. It also says start here. Okay. So if we go to see, let me see. I need to
Um, I'm see if clubs is on it yet because there's over 21 pictures 21 pages of guests
There's like 500 guests. Can you imagine 500 guests? Like that's a lot of everybody has been here in the show
Yeah, so a lot of fucking working to this shit. Oh, it's everything. Yeah, it's all
Everybody's on everybody every show everything everything. Let me see if clubs is on it yet. See HH
Body's showing. Okay. Come to clear avoid. I don't know if your newest episodes are on yet
So I don't think you're on it yet, but you will be there's crystals on it. See five up here. You will be
Five crystals appearances also everyone that was on the show who she appears with
And then there's like, you know, there's an even shorts are there
And it has the whole summary of every episode.
There has a transcript of every episode,
like see the transcript, the whole transcript there, right?
It'll have some quotes from the show.
And then you can also sign in and you can like start,
I'm talking and like post stuff to yourself
and have a discussion about the show.
So it's a whole ecosystem.
There's topics, how many topics are there?
There's like 2,500 topics that we've talked about
and everything is there, 102 pages of that, right?
And everything, like whatever your,
interested in what you can search this and you can find any episode any guest and watch all the episodes on it
So I think it's pretty cool. So pretty much it's like your own like domain pretty much
Yeah, it's called the codex and it's like it's just all it does is it just catalogs everything and it makes it easily searchable
And it puts all the transcripts on it because I was told like oh, you don't have transcripts
I have
Well, the ai did um do some of the transcription for the episodes that don't have transcripts and stuff
Oh, he's back. Okay. Hold on one second
Okay, that's a lot of fucking work though. I have been working on it probably for six months and stuff
But there's several false starts in there where I like it's so I'm look clumsy
Are you guys saying oh, I'm on a list
You guys are on a list
Palin's here. Well, that was rain. That's the bed in the chat
Rain said you don't you look like you're on a list, but you don't you just maybe the most
Calm down, I think that's where you and clumsy, you know
We all agree like those are like the worst people, right?
But let's like not get into that because it's too controversial a topic for my show. It's not what my show is about
Yeah, they need they really need to get some help and stuff like that and you know kind of be separated, right?
But let's let's calm down on that shit, okay?
It's not what the topics about it's not what my shows about is like, you know, it's about
Coming together and not like about all these divisive things, you know
it could be based on any other topic besides fucking kids and
Exactly and I think that's like the worst thing to say I don't want to bring it up even in a pleasant context
They got yeah, it's like we should be left to 21 and over
Let's just leave it to 21 and over people and leave people's families and kids and everything else out of it
Don't even say the word unless you're referring to actual
You know, I'm not I'm not trying to like rouse shit up. I mean, it's already out there because they're pretty much talking about it
But I thought a certain group of people kept was gonna keep their words saying they were gonna bring your name up
But yet their whole fucking streams based on you, bro
How they expect not so in the fucking react just a little bit. You know what I mean or a reaction
Right. I mean, it's like because they have a list of people like oh if you're on this show in that show
then here's the names like Zaya, Pebs, and you know, Samman, and Vita, blah, blah, blah. But
I'm not on that list because she won't say my name, but she will say fraudulent psychic.
She will say spiritual trafficker and things like that, like just and making it obvious who I
and I was her friend, you know, I was like, and I did I did I ever do anything to cross her? No,
I just questioned her once. Are you turning against me because she was doing some kind of
Because I asked her that she turned against me. I mean, it was like some
Beta no, we're talking about Alexander right there. Oh, okay. Okay. I thought that you're talking about
Beta two Beta two is like, oh, don't talk about me. You keep it and then she has a whole streams about me
Like today's whole stream was pretty much about me
Yeah, I'm I'm not gonna lie like I put can pop in and first thing right out there fucking
My mouth was psyche this I'm like man
I was like y'all y'all want him to stop reacting to y'all but y'all keep on but then you have these people that are trying to
make
shit
neutral between y'all, but how do you make shit neutral if you're sitting there constantly talking shit
Because then I hear myself and it's like I did come she I mean she I'll to give her props
She did let me up and you know she got porn bombed and so then I didn't come up after that
But she did like say oh, I'm banned and then she like let me up and stuff so she I mean there's something there
That is like there's still something there
Okay, like there's some kind of affection. There's some kind of like something but it's like there's all this animosity about
Something said six months ago by somebody else and this and this person that person and there's all these people that will come up
And just attack and then it's like she's kind of maybe a certain group doesn't like another certain group
But the okay picture this imagine two leaders that get along right two kings, but
The the kings man on both sides don't see eye to eye
It's kind of like in that situation, it's also like in this community, you know
People like to stir shit up and so that's when the beginning
It's like people would come over here and say she's saying this about you and she wasn't or I'm saying this about her
and then we kind of like
Trust some of these people and so we'll say oh exactly
That's my whole point of saying that with the whole you know
With the leaders and man because you know you think they have the best intentions for you
But they could be plotting on some other shit
These people could be plotting with these people these people could be plotting give what I'm saying
It's just a big old fucking mix of bullshit
Yeah, a lot of it is about like stirring shit up and like caught and also, you know if you will see like a
That's why people don't show their spouses on the show.
It's because any time there's like real true love
or there's like true affection or there's true friendship,
it'll be attacked.
It'll be attacked in just to, I don't know if it's a test
or if it's like just to like turn things around on that.
But it's like, it's a million times.
I remember one time my wife, you know, she was on the, she was on a panel and she was
on my stream, but it wasn't like I was showing her face or anything.
It was just like a quick, like, you know, couple conversations, whatever.
And then all of a sudden you have my book is like Sam Man saying, oh, well, you're,
you're wife's part of the community now and never have I brought my wife or
None of this shit, you know
Other part of the community, right?
Yeah, they try to attack me with these fucking little profile pics of oh
Clumsy so-and-so crumbs ease of this member this man. I don't get well fuck
You know what I mean at the end of the day? I really don't
Because when they're looking at them fucking profiles, they're gonna really get a fucking
Yeah, yeah, they're gonna understand but like I said, you know, it would be different if I would put my spouse on here
But like you said a lot of people don't do that because the sorry-ass people around here
Yeah, I mean it's sad. I mean it isn't really sad how
like, you know
People really do want dissension. They want arguments. They want the drama and stuff and that's what they do
And that's why JT and you don't show yourselves because people can be weird. Yeah, that's smart too
But it's at the same time. I do show myself and and I have since the beginning and there's people that don't show themselves
That are just so happy to
Attack on a multiple all they make themselves look bigger like an army or something just by going on like 10 accounts each and like
They look like 30 people instead of three people, right?
Well, I I've seen that video that a
Joker posted about the fucking views bro, and you know what if that boy knows
Anything about the fucking internet and how fucking bots and all that shit fucking goes it would be
It would be him. You know what I mean? I mean, there's other people that could probably, you know, call it out what he did, but
You know, you really start to
Think about, you know, I'm not saying that every fucking
Streamer has body views, but it's just kind of crazy that you don't even have like maybe
20 active people in the chat, but yet there's a hundred and something it and not there's no fucking way
Yeah, I mean it's like I mean
And that's not me being a hater like hey if you're pulling those numbers and they're real cool shot to you
Whatever, you know what I mean, but you know to be real like you pull your like the way Joker kind explaining
You pull natural numbers, bro. You don't need no fucking box, right?
I don't I don't and it's like and I've had 500 people in here
there are there are actually 100 real people and things like that and I don't know and I know she
has a very active chat she has very loyal people and all that but if you look at it it's like
a lot of the people are the same what would you rather have though what would you rather have
20 loyal people or 80 fucking hate watching fucking trolls fake and I do have a lot of
hate watchers here like there's 30 people there's probably like five to ten people chatting and stuff
Yeah, I mean, yeah, if you clumsy you want your link. Yeah, can you post to clumsy's a link Jamie? That'd be great
You know like clumsy does have a he does. He's a streamer. I don't know if you always been a streamer or like you just been doing
Honestly, it was something that I really despise on for a while
But then I kind of like gave it to it in a way, you know
Join all these panels and then once good times like was doing his own thing like to wear
People couldn't even go up anymore. People wanted a panel. You know people wanted other spots to chill and
You know
Is like good times like so good times
You know he had his channel take it down his main channel and then he came up on an alternative channel
And he had like, you know, did it what he wants to do all chat and stuff. I I joined
I think Christina is there and Christina joins and then Christina not actually having a good conversation like one-on-one working stuff out
Calm both calm both getting their points across then
Bita shows up and then
Sweepie shows up and then Sandman shows up and all of a sudden it's just like pile on me
And it's like I have to yell to give my people and discourse like watching they're like hey
They're watching like all different streams that are live. They're like, okay. Well, this person's over there
Let's all go over there and uh, that's what it seems like bro. It's like a bunch of fucking this. Yeah a group of this
I don't know and I'd be happy to talk to any of them one-on-one, but it's like
Why do they need a group of four against one? I mean, that's really not exactly exactly but at the end of the day
What what are you gonna get done? How many times have you had these?
You know conversation with and I'm not saying it can't be resolved because anything can be resolved
It just depends on both sides of the party. Yeah, and it's like and when it's like people in each other's ears say
Oh, you're right. You're right. It's like and then people get
And it just turns that people, it's kind of like, it's kind of like, it's kind of like those,
maybe you have a schoolyard, like, you know, fight where it's just like,
there's certain people around this person to remember, and everyone's like, go, go,
and everyone just wants to see a fight, basically, at the end of the day.
It is, of course, of course, I mean.
At the end of the day, you know, you have your supporters, but then you also attracted, you know, a different crowd of people, you know, associate, I'm not saying you associate with them, but people that popped up on your panel, people that, you know what I mean, that's clipped you, you know, you get around, bro, it's almost like free promotion, even though they might try to put you in a bad light.
It's like promotion either fucking way you look right, but there are some things that are said that are just so outrageous
And it's like yeah, and then oh, yeah
She's mad about things that people say in my chat, but it's like she's got mods literally mods saying
Animal abuser and oh like I remember one night. It was all about I am abused my cats
My cats are starving. They have fleas. They're all they're all dying and stuff like that
And I'm like hey, and then it's like also
They lied too, like that sweepy person.
Like yesterday she posted something
after we had that conversation,
I had to apologize to her.
She posted something, it said donate to me or else
or something and I'm like going through a window
just like that, you know, the Alexander Mayer meme
or I'm like, like in this like scary, like, you know,
just like asking for donations in an aggressive way.
But I was like, oh, too.
And then so I was like, okay, well.
And that was my actual image that she's using. So I just use I took her image and I made a cartoonish
Image where she's three her pounds has sweepy on her belly and stuff. But you saw them you saw, right? Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, that's another thing and I'm not saying, you know all these
Females that don't come up or big whatever there's no problem being big
But when you're big yourself and you're fat shaming other big girls, it's kind of like
Yeah, that was it. You know what I mean? Like like I've always been honest about some shit
Like I've always been the big girls. I've always I'm just that's the type of person I am
But when you have people that are comfortable with their self and they're pretty much
and they're pretty much talking about their own cell, bro.
I didn't understand shit like that, bro.
It's Samantha.
I mean, yeah, so, I mean, I posted that,
but it's like, it's a cartoon.
It's obviously like a joke.
And you know, it's like, you know, she's not,
but she has you cammed up ever, but does she have it?
Obviously, it's Joe.
This is nothing but banter, bro,
but these people take it fucking to the heart.
They want to be playing victim.
They want to stay there and be a fucking bully,
but when you fucking turn around, be a bully back,
they want to play victim.
That's exactly the way I fucking see it. Oh, well, let's go
Laugh at this clip that this person made. Oh, ha ha
He was psyche did it's so disgusting and and grow test and then yeah, yeah
Like what the fuck you're just in there fucking mopping your fucking mouth with all these other pieces of shit
This and this and this but man come on
Yeah, I mean it's like right
I have a creativity and I have an ability to,
ability to, you know, generate funny things too.
And it's like, but you know,
but the funny thing was Sheila's laughing about it.
I don't think she's that big, but she doesn't like,
when I said that, she was very offended,
which is kind of-
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
She was like, I'm not 600 pounds.
Okay, well, can you can't, it just shows your,
shows your body then, like, I mean, like,
or just like, you know, you don't have to show your face.
Just like, it's okay.
I don't care if she's 600 pounds or not.
She was just irritated her and she does stuff that irritates me like don't show me bald
And then what does she have she has me as Cyrax now she has me getting hit in the head with a biscuit and like
The majority of these people that have always something to say about someone's appearance like people talk try to climb on my tooth
Like honestly, it's coming from fucking faceless fucking trolls right this trolls, right?
You can't if you actually honestly there was a point when I would say probably within a couple years, bro
I've learned I've learned a lot of bullshit. I was I was a dumbass listening to everyone and I didn't know what the fuck was going on
And I'm new to the fucking internet point blank. So I'm new to all this
You know, if you let this shit honestly take a toll, you know, it's gonna fucking drive you fucking crazy
Someone says I said the Edward to black people. So I said maybe said it to sandman and lady bad
Said the inward sandman said the inward beta said the inward like
Right, but if I say it, it's like a scandal.
I mean, if I say it, it's like,
oh, I'm clipped on rumble, and you know,
it's just like, now I'm racist,
when I didn't say it against any kind of like,
person of any kind of race, that is a big knife, huh?
And the people that complain about it
been complaining about years,
but if it was really a big problem,
and they didn't, if they felt disgusted by
how everything is the n-word, why are they still here?
I don't know. I mean, it's just shocking.
And like I said, I'm gay and it's like,
you see, I haven't been called names in my life.
I am. Do you think I haven't been called names in my life?
It's like the sixth grade or whatever.
Back at a million times.
And we call it by Vita and stuff like that.
And it's like, but it's like, if I say anything,
it's a scandal.
Where's Johnny maybe taking the night off. I love Johnny and I you know, but I think you might be taking the night off
You know
She's been really really having my back lately
Yeah, I do have a nice. This is a nice. I got these bagels. I got like
Bakers dozen of bagels the deluxe bagels with two cream cheeses for it's like $35 with the bagels for like 10 bucks on the app
You know, watch those logos
This is a onion and shive
That's a little if for me though when I eat bagels I usually put like the was it like the strawberry Philadelphia fucking cream keys and all that shit like yeah
They have a hot honey right now the hot honey is like popular and spicy
That's not bad I'm not gonna lie like in the morning that's not bad bro
I've had it in the morning a couple of times you know like I need this gaming well I mean I wish they had a garlic they don't have the garlic bagels at this place but they
Yeah, but um, I got, yeah, this is my, oh, and then they say, I have, please, my, you're, you're, hey, Tracy, because he'll, he'll scratch a little, they can't scratch a little, they're not covered in, please, they really aren't, they are indoor outdoor cats.
Oh, you want, you want to have some bagel?
Awesome.
I
Know it's like people like, you know, it was always like I would eat my parents, you know, my parents plates
They're like we have the same germs. I think I have the same germs as my cat. No, that's your cat. Yeah, that's it's your baby
You know saying believe I know people that that
Treat their fucking darling. They actually like brush their teeth. They do all that. I'm not saying that you have to do that
You know, I mean, it's your fucking animal. You can do whatever you want with it
but um, yeah, don't don't don't let them fucking sit there and
They'll be making like peanut butter jelly sandwiches that cuz my cousin does his shit, bro
And she has a was a dormant pincher
Yeah, he fucking loves peanut butter, bro
And she'll be sitting there eating peanut butter off the fucking spoon
Hurry now. I'm like we have a guest. I have to find my mouse one second. Where's my mouse?
Shit. Oh, here it is. I get you. It's tricks. We're sitting on it. Let's welcome the beautiful
But I think where's the Duke's had a song with the Duke's of Heather's team songs, you know
I don't know the Duke's of Heather's team song
There you go. Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, man
Hey
Hey, can I gotta ask you a question? Sure. I don't mean to start no shit. Okay. Yeah
You gave me a wrench. It took it away
He gave me a wrench this time after I told you not to and you took it away again. You're in chat
All right, you're in chat. Are you in chat? Okay, you're the right. Why did you do that?
Because I constantly am unmodding and remodding people because but it wasn't personal. It's just like I'm on it everybody
Yeah, it was it all it was all you have it back right now
Yeah, he did he did the same to me and I told him I was like out of respect psyche. I fuck with you
Just don't make me mob. You know what I mean?
Well, I did that for a long time. I said, you know, don't fucking marred me, right?
Because I don't like it. Because I don't do anything with it anyways.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It was out of respect. That's why I give it...
I don't expect you to do anything. I just give it to you out of respect.
Well, the reason why I kept it this time without bitching about it
is because, you know, you're changing back to your old psyche, you know?
I am.
Are you coming around as for you clumsy? I gotta bet you about you nothing personal well
Yeah, it is personal
It is you done me dirty, dude. Oh, I need an apology
What did I do? Oh
I'd say about a month ago. I was up on panel
and fucking you did the same thing Bita did
and didn't even warn me that Trisha Licious was coming on
and you knew she was gonna attack me.
And then you sat back and did nothing.
And I left the fucking panel.
From what I remember, Tracy,
and I can look back on the video,
I think I did say that Trisha Licious was coming up
because you were talking about her.
And when music, two people have a problem,
I let them talk it out.
I didn't say that she was going up.
I was unprepared.
But if she's in my face,
and I thought we were better friends than them.
No, and I understand that.
And if you built some type of way
about the administration, I apologize.
You know what I mean?
I kind of understand this way of coming from.
I understand this way of coming from content too,
you know what I mean?
Well, I don't use it for content though.
I don't, I don't.
I just thought we were better friends than that.
Cause, you know, and I think we still act.
Yeah, of course
Yeah, once you calm down, then you talk to the person
You know, of course, we level fucking head of course, of course. And like I said, you know, if you felt disrespected
I'm gonna fucking be a man about it. And if that's how you feel, I apologize, you know
I accept your apology man big time because I really like you a lot
You know that and like I said if I would have known that you know what I mean
I
I didn't I didn't hear it and if you said it then you know, it's both of our fault
I'll double look and like like I said well either way even if it if I did or didn't I'm gonna double look either way but
I'm still gonna be a man enough if you that's right because we're friends man
But I'm you know
And I'm not hollering at you screaming at you
Of course, you know, that's why I stayed away from you for a while because I was upset and I I didn't know
So I didn't want to comment
You know what I mean?
No, and I just tied you over.
And you know what?
You did that out of respect too,
because I know you would have probably been like,
hey, you know, let me.
I'd attack you like another fucking thing.
You know, and I'm not that way.
I know, Ms. Tracy.
I know.
But I'm all fucked up tonight.
Hey, there ain't no wrong with this shit.
We all go for it.
I got me goddamn Gucci.
I got some good shit.
Start out to you, Ms. Trace.
I'm going to use a restroom.
Give me a sec.
Tracey have you been you know my Russian friend really liked you
I mean and she and she's um, you know, unfortunately, I think she got in a car accident
She's really upset last night. She said she's all right. She's all right. I think the car her car is not good
She's like my life is over. I just crashed my another car or whatever. How old is she? She is
probably about
40 she's almost 40. I think you know, she's like five years or six years younger than me. So
It's nice, like red Mercedes Benz, I think, and, you know, and she's been doing really
well otherwise.
I'm going to try to, she's charging my phone, so I'm going to tell her that you're here
and stuff, because she was like, oh, I'm going to come up with one when Tracy's there, because
she really, she really enjoyed you and stuff, and you're so cool.
And I, you know, and, you know, I mean, it's hard in this community, you know, it's a hard
But dude, we gotta fucking stick together.
If you're gonna be friends,
then you gotta be able to talk about something and say,
hey, look, did you mean to do this?
You know, without screaming at each other.
Yeah.
You know?
And then some people really don't care
if they're about the mod is that,
but some people it's like a,
it's like a, it's like a token of the friendship.
And so-
Well, it was a big thing to us
because I wouldn't take a mod for a long time
because I was-
I didn't want to be a part of your crew. I just wanted to be a guest
Well, you know
last night I went on beatas and I
Said the n-word several times
To some people that really they're not they're not they're not black or anything
I just don't understand you
Right over there rock in the first place. I know
You beat the fuck out of yourself
I do you do you like to be punished at the police came also last night because I
Was yelling so loud and I get so upset and stuff
Okay, we have a big guest here. We have a guest. Let's welcome
Hallelujah, hallelujah, hallelujah, hallelujah
Hey everyone, how are you? Tracy, how you doing?
Oh, I'm very well, very well
Good, good to see you, Psyche, how you doing, man? Clumsy, what's good?
This is a bathroom. Oh, you know God, you know Tracy. Yeah, I was way back. I remember Tracy
We we met in 79 wasn't a Tracy long time ago. Oh, yeah
Right down highway 85. I remember I had a flat tire
He gave me a hand. I'll never forget that
I just happen to have an impact. Oh good times good times. Yeah
How's everyone tonight everyone have a good night?
Oh, hell yeah.
Oh, fuck, good times, good times.
Nothing like eating a bagel at two o'clock in the morning.
Ha, ha, ha.
Fuck yeah.
Shit.
If a clumsy passed out, huh, that's like a guy.
Oh, I'm coming.
He talks a good game.
I'm talking for a long time.
Clumsy can't hang.
He tries, but he can't hang.
He's the light-weight.
Hey, we went to the bathroom.
He's gonna piss.
Did you wash your hands before you ate that bagel?
Clean hands clean life, bro. That's how I live man clean hands clean life
You don't know what you're touching man. That's right. You never know when the feces is gonna be
You see that where they averaging out 42,000 fucking
College people got fucking STDs from Houston
Wow
that's great you did oh god in 2000 all the way from age to fucking syphilis to everything
well you know i've never had an std because i grew up in the 80s and as a child i just grew up saying
Gay people get a lot of gay people die like a lot of people a lot of gay people did die in the 80s
you know of that and
I've always been disease-phobic and so I'm I'm really not into like sleeping around
I mean, I know my kind of a slut
Personality online sometimes excuse me, but I'm really not I'm really more
When the 80s came out and AIDS came out that's when we all zipped our bridges up
Yeah
Because it was like I think the story there's something called the guy and I'm the band played on there's a book called the band played on
It's about the origin of the HIV thing and it was about a bisexual
African
Flight attendants and he would sleep with all these men around the world right on the other thing on flights and stuff
Yeah, that's basically what spread it all around the world, right?
It's a day flight attempt. We've got blame for everything, right? Yeah, my first husband died of it. I'm sorry
Yeah, it's very serious. You think you watched the you watched the video?
I'm just glad I left in time where I didn't get it. Yeah
I mean, it is something that is like, I think more difficult to get than people thought it was to get, but it's like there were when people are on drugs and they're having
Unpredicted sex for hours and hours.
that I think is like really increases the chances of that I mean in the gay community at least because that you know
They have the methamphetamine they had a whole gay or a whole of AIDS crisis in San Francisco is a huge psychic
You have AIDS Peter South. I'm sorry. I don't you have you ever actual disease. I'm sorry if you do if you do because
Don't quite believe you because nowadays people really don't get that anymore like now. There's medications and nothing
You're in Africa and don't be on the med for life though, you know
Yeah, you do but it's like it is one pill a day which is like, you know
a lot different. They used to have like cocktails of like, you know, 10 different pills and stuff to keep to keep it down
But nowadays if you take one pill, you're in Africa. Oh my gosh, Peter South. I'm so sorry. You have it. You're an African
I didn't know I didn't know
Yeah, they should run rampant
But have you seen any of the Alexander Mayer's stuff going on? I refuse to watch that bitch, too. You don't like her well
You know, she now she says that this is actually a real cult and
Because I like, you know, I'm interested in the goddess Lilith. She said it's like a
It's sacrificing, you know
Cult right of you know, this is the worst it says that you need to paste
Right. She also doesn't say my name. She calls me just the fraudulent psychic
Even though she had more than probably 10 paid readings from me
That's why I don't like that woman, she's all trouble.
Yeah, she's trouble.
And she turned on me for no reason too.
And I'm not gonna ever let anybody forget
that all I asked her was, are you turning on me?
And then she just turned on me.
That was it.
All I had to ask if she was, and that was it.
I warned you, she did the same to me.
I did. I warned you it's difficult. I mean it's difficult because they know we had a great dinner together
Yeah, but you're fucking stupid and keep going back, you know, but and I and I but now she's doing shows about me
I do like to see what's being said about me sometimes
See, I don't want to watch it at all
If I don't like somebody then I don't go near them because I don't like them. I don't want to hear the voice
I don't want to see them that I'm done
I consider her a close friend at one point.
She would call it at midnight.
We talk until like three or four in the morning sometimes.
Just about everything, you know, but now I think it was collecting information. Hey, man, Erickson. Hey 2020
You know, no person's little if you rather no person's little sign rather than their son sign
See that the littlest is the exact that's like the dark side, right?
It's like it's also like his little it likes to be in the dark cave
She's just she doesn't want to be in the light. She wants to be away from every everybody
I mean if you know about astrology, and that's basically I take it as an astrological
the dark side, but it takes it as like a literal, like...
You know, oh this person is sacrificing babies and and all this kind of stuff and it's like
She said I'm working for the Mexican mafia. She literally said she's her last stream is called drug cartels and
and and
Deven worshipers and it says oh, that's she said the Mexican mafia is hiring
Psyche to do magic for them, but he's not I mean it's like so crazy
I mean, I wish I could get some business from Mexican mafia.
Maybe I'd have a little bit of a bigger business, but no, no, they haven't contacted me here.
I mean, it's crazy. I mean, but it really, it's like, what the fuck?
Where, what part of her ass is she pulling this information from or this idea?
I mean, did you see Tracy? I just have to show you this.
Look what she posted of me recently. Look at this picture. I mean, this is like
and she posted like several of these pictures, but here's the worst one I think, this is like
look at this one, do you see this?
yes I see it
you saw that one?
oh my god, no I haven't seen it, I like I said don't pay attention to more
that's supposed to be, this is supposed to be a beta and saman
Pretty mean of a burning dumpster. This is imagine claiming to be a powerful and a knowledgeable
Practitioner but failing to realize you're the literal sacrifice of a Jewish
Missus is this is a rooted ritual designed to complete the process of manifesting militant semi
Semial into the world and that's what she literally posted and then she posted this one too of like
I'm sorry, if you don't tell me James, tell me James.
Tell me James, like she posted this one of James and Crystal
and I, and this one says, tell my desktop.
Okay, one second.
This one says, is that the right one?
I got it.
Yeah, look at this one.
Oh, no, that's sorry, that's clumsy.
Oh my God.
That's clumsy in good times.
Well, she has clumsy, good times, good times door.
Good times.
It's a watermelon and these are the one Jesus
Yeah, what the fuck oh, I didn't even notice the KFC in the water
And she's actually she actually said she thinks I got good times channel taken down and
That I stole good times style. I wear flannel shirts
But my first my father passed away a couple years ago
He loved those flannel shirts and I got a bunch of his flannel shirts
So I wear flannel shirts once in a while, but it's cuz not cuz I'm trying to steal good times's stuff or anything
But then she posted the one more. I'll show you this is that the last one. I think it's this one right here
Yeah, this is look at this one. This is crazy
Oh, man, she got fucking my donation.
That's the story.
There's baby Tommy James who's balding,
and then there's Crystal Ann.
They said, I hate my Korean eyes,
and Tommy James one says, I hate,
or it's like, I'm balding,
and I'm, and then there's Aaron Carter,
the hero and stuff.
I mean, I just,
and I'm like this monster outside the window.
But we're trying to get baby Tommy James and and Crystal Anne and see that's where you and I are different man
I I fucking somebody do you dirty. I don't give him any ammo. I don't give him any watch time. I'll give him shit
You know
I'm not in, but you run a show, so you need to run it.
You see that.
And you know, I'm still here.
I'm still here.
I'm still, hey, I'm not, I haven't been shamed off of why.
The worst stuff's upset about me.
I mean, the worst, now, you know,
they go after me and my cats and stuff.
Oh, you know, Christine was like,
oh, even your cats hate you.
You're to watch today's stream.
I had Lenora like basically trying to friend kids
and I had to like say, Lenora, down a little,
because Lenora is just like, she loves me so much.
and I love my cat so much, Crystal Ann.
Crystal Ann is like in the Carterverse.
She's kind of friends with like a-
If your cat's fucking hated you, Psyche,
you would have all kinds of fucking scratches on your face.
You'd be getting attacked and-
You wouldn't be here,
because cats don't fuck around with people
that are mean to them.
You know, cats don't-
Oh hell no, there was a stray cat
that a buddy of mine's girlfriend adopted, right?
And it was a stray cat.
and this they thought because it was smaller whatever whatever it was young okay that cat
did not like neither one of them every time they had the chance bro it would attack them
literally attack their face anywhere that could get skin it would go for the skin it knew like
the clothes was like a cloth like kind of like a like a armor for any extra skin straight skin
All right, my bad restriction died. Just want to jump up and say hi to you. I love you Tracy. I you're you're monogat, okay?
Always
I love you. See you. Love you Tracy. Have a good night
Look at this cat. Look at this. Look at this cat
Love you. It's like a cat that you love her fucking eyes, bro. Yeah, this is miss Lenore
She's a sweetheart. She's my baby
See, I'm not gonna lie like my mom's always been up
She's always go catch her. Her thing is always sigmes sigmes. Yeah, well
the only cat that I own personally was a calico and
Someone stole my cat
Oh, yeah, that kind of hurt bro. I'm not gonna like cuz I had that cat
I hope the cat's okay and stuff, you know, I'm pretty sure it was cuz no
Bro, all that cat would do would eat sleep and shit that cat was bro
I bet it wasn't no table straps nothing, but I kept that cat eating fucking good-ass fucking food, bro
good-ass fucking cat food and
Now like I see everyone getting cats even like buddies of mine have fucking cats like my homeboy has a cow
No, exactly. He told me to breed but the cat it's fucking ears are like
Like uh kind of almost like a you know what a links looks like right? Yeah, they're like a little bit bigger
They're kind of skinny and like
Yes, but it's a cat. It's a it's actually a fucking cat
But it's like a rare kind of like exotic cat. He said I don't know does that mean is there exotic cats?
Yeah, it's an exotic cat is kind of like almost half jungle cat or only a wild cat
Slinks, you know, it's like it's like a more it's a more wild kind of cat and the cats like white with beige on it
Like the the the beige is like like a reddish beige in the way like kind of like a I
Don't know like a I
Wouldn't say like a brandy color cuz that's too dark. I don't know real but that that cat's first. It's beautiful
The way it looks beautiful, but the thing about I just want to get me a small dog
We need a small dog. Yeah. Well, I would say, you know, I grew up with a Maltese when I went out
Like the Maltese are very spoiled like little dogs like these to be just like they always be in the island of Malta
They think things would have this Maltese cat in their like robes and they would have changed their diaper and stuff
They would just they would
They're just pampered them. There's a little pampered white dogs
I sort of grew up around but I would say or that or like a little Yorkie like a little Yorkie tear like these little like
The miniature Yorkies and stuff. Those are so cute. Yeah, the little furry ones and shit
Yeah, I see no because I want to be able to have a small dog to where I could get like a
like they call it a dog a dog shelter purse whatever the fuck you want to call it because
If I'm gonna have an animal like that, bro, I'm gonna be treating the animal like if it's my child, you know what I mean
I'd rather have, yeah, I mean, even a major sized dog
would be cool, but it's just better to have a small size.
Like if I get a teacup chihuahua, that's my first go.
If I can't get that, a regular chihuahua.
If not, then maybe we'll go for like a Yorkie
or something like that, but a pug, something,
you know what I mean?
Pug, that's Sweepee's latest thing
where she's eating with a biscuit in the face, you know?
What the fuck?
Sweepies latest one to kill them with a biscuit
I'm being hit in the face with the I think I can't there's a KFC biscuit or something like that
What is the whole what's the whole lore behind the whole biscuit shit, bro?
Well, I mean, it's like it kept being talked about and I was like it has to be something more than just I got like a
KFC
KFC like biscuit because they're like laughing so hard about it and I think it's like an inside joke
Then one day in my feed it popped up. Oh look at the new biscuit coming up
It's like a this black. It's like a hockey puck and it's like this Wi-Fi spy device
And so I was like maybe that's what they're talking about like it's kind of like spying device or something
And there's like laughing about I don't know but
right pretty much it's like an insight thing for for for them like yeah it's
like it's like an inside joke that all I've been left out of but just it's been
been used at me like oh he doesn't know what it means so it's funny and stuff
like that because they they just keep saying it over and over I mean it was
just like some stupid
It was a real biscuit it literally wouldn't be like that big of a joke
Yeah, I never understood that I was like, okay, maybe psyche got a fucking door-dash
I'm like a hundred biscuits to his fucking house or something
They're bags of concrete if you don't want to me a hundred biscuits. I would like that
You know, I got, I got, I got a hundred, I got a hundred bags of concrete, 60 bag concrete, and that's like 6,000 pounds of concrete at my door, you know, and I was like, I was able to give it all away because when I was making a swimming pool, like, luckily, but, you know, it's not cool.
I mean, it's like, I'm trying to tell my Russian friend to come over here, because it's not concrete though, like, why?
Like in all reality of people got the time and all that shit and like you say
I think you had told me that some of the concrete got messed up in the rain
But like if that concrete was all like for go you could have made some money out that shit
But I understand you want to get you're rid of that shit. Just yeah, you know what I mean?
Yeah, I mean it's like
Yeah, because
I would have loved to like, you know,
but then again, I don't want to be known in the neighborhood.
Oh, here, you know, I'm gonna get it
to six, seven pounds of concrete.
And then they're like, what is this guy about?
They're like, so I basically, somebody came over
to their detailing in my neighbor's car
and I was listening out the window and they're like,
oh my God, look at that concrete.
They're like, can I take some of that?
And the guy's like, yeah, because, you know,
this guy keeps getting sent concrete.
And he's like, yeah, I'm redoing my,
I'm remodeling my swimming pool.
And then the next thing I know, I went down.
but it's all taken away
yeah I mean
it's not like you lost all any money
you could have made some money
but it's not like you lost out on anything
I didn't lose out on anything
it's just a bad
it looks bad when you get out of the FX
30 bags of concrete outside your house
and the neighbors were like
what the fuck is this about
and there's people coming back
with trucks
of concrete and stuff like in my and I feel bad because what if what if one of the guys that are
delivering the concrete is like some older dude you get what I'm saying like oh no no but okay
listen there's like there's probably a 90 year old Asian man came up he's like hello the weed wacker
I was like, no, I'm not giving away a weed wacker.
He drove like two hours from somewhere, you know,
this guy to get the weed wacker that supposedly
I was giving away.
Do they have these Craigslist ads that say,
oh, you know, I'm giving away this stuff.
And they'll say, go knock on his door really loud.
My wife's on a Zoom call and stuff, just knock really loud.
And it's annoying, it's supposed to be annoying.
And I know who it is to the doing it and stuff.
But basically,
After a while, I think I think it's finally they're banned on Craigslist or something because it's really slowed down
I do get I did get some way I delivering pizza. Yeah, someone trying to turn off the water yesterday
I had someone trying to turn off the electricity sometimes
I got someone trying to turn off the all the utilities, right?
They said people they said people for emergency. Oh gas leak and stuff like that come come over and they're and they're like
They're like about to do it without asking me. Yeah, and
I got rid of all the concrete, of course.
Of course I did it.
One way or another, I'll either take one bag a week
and throw it in the dumpster, or someone took it all away.
But basically, they can't do it anymore.
I think DoorDash changed their policy, finally,
because they let some guy deliver like 30 pounds,
or 30 bags of the 60-pound concrete,
and then they were like,
I went down and said stop. I said please like not put that down there and just take it away
He's like no. Oh, he said he said is he's insane nephew or something was there gonna say don't put it there, right?
Right, this is just crazy. It's absolutely fucking crazy, right? And it's like I was like, no, no, he's harassing me
And this is our lead. I'm on the police. I'm like
I mean, it's it's fucking crazy for someone to be fucking with you utilities. Oh, like come on. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, and that's illegal because once that that once that happened
He started calling the police like the utility companies would start calling the police because that was like a
Major probably two hours from someplace to come become it's crazy
like even I'm not saying these people are hacking anything because that's they're gonna probably make fun of me and say
I'm even saying this shit, but I mean
How can I put it?
Just forget what I was going to say, just forget it.
Okay, it's just fucking crazy, it's like...
I lose the words to, to, to express it too, cause it's just so cruel and there's no reason
for it.
It's this bisexual guy that's like insecure with sexuality and maybe I said he was bisexual
or something.
And then he's like getting back at me.
He's now they're putting family members as, as a accounts and putting their pictures and
names and stuff out there and stuff.
And it's like, what can I do about this stuff?
I can report it.
Does YouTube do shit about this?
You know and then on top of that too, you know the people that you that you most likely know that's probably doing it
They're not gonna get their hands dirty, bro
They're gonna but now because of this because of it all because people do not understand that it's so unfair
I have been told their city their state their full name their birth. I mean so now
I mean, I've done the OSINT thing.
I don't know if you know what OSINT is.
You know what OSINT is?
I heard of it, but I don't know exactly too much.
There's like websites you can like basically.
Get some kind of information and then like oh like like out of country types. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay
You can basically track everything down like one by one year you can put the information
You get some information from here the information there if I'm more information
I mean yeah, because there's certain she here United States. That's illegal to do but in other fucking countries
Oh, yeah, like another one's gonna use my P2. He said we're we've ruined lives for sport
He said you and Alex McQueen are both like docs on the IPT website and we're gonna like swat you tomorrow and stuff like that
And it's like
You're kind of like your blood pressure grows up a little bit like what the fuck and then nothing happens, right?
It's just basically lie. There's basically just to scare you
Now we have to be on your toes because
When I'm I'm not gonna say here and say take every threat serious, but you know
My friend Danny was I don't know if Danny was just
Killed by a random person or there was somebody trying to get initiated in some kind of society
And it hated him because he was online and stuff
And then was waiting for me the gas station his local gas station and shot him three times in the chest like a couple weeks ago
Right, that's my friend Danny. That was a promoting. That's crazy. He's dead. I mean he was shot three times in the chest
Well, it's not the dude that introduced me into the hole
Before it was IP to
He was recently found shot in a parking lot with I think a shot in the head and two shots in the chest
And if it wasn't for him, I wouldn't have found this community. Honestly, I wouldn't
I probably wouldn't be here right now
Right
No, and it's like something happened to Benny. I would feel so horrible and it's like it's been you know, Benny and Trident and like
Joker and all these people that's why I saw you for the first time was on Joker's channel, right?
I went over there and then Joker like even said like last night. He's like, hey, he's that I got psyche
I told thank you to start a sort of podcast or whatever and he's like and look what look at this now
And it's like I want now I want to help these people because it's like, you know some of these people like have
Pretty small channel or they don't have that many people coming. I don't know why I have 39 people in the chat, right?
I don't I don't know it's like I don't know like what it is and there's not that many people chatting or stuff
I mean there's people also in here that fuck with you, you know me, but then also you're gonna have your hate watchers, of course
Yeah, hey watchers, but I still have a like I've got great like you can see most people are mods in the chat
Yeah, you got more support than anything, but even the hate watchers are low-key your fans if you look at
a lot of it is. And it's like, and I got such great, I just, I just, I'm so lucky because
I do have people that like
help me to and but I put that out too like I want to help people too as a thing
You find me entertaining and not hate worthy. Thank you tech deck dude, but you don't do nothing that bad though
So you can compare to other motherfuckers around here. You don't do anything
So it's crazy because I've heard into the devil now and I've turned into like oh, I'm like
I just say this is not and it's like I've always been like
Hey support these people. I anyone wants to get started channel
I'll I'll help you get your first 15 subscribers and you can like start doing live
I mean, I was so happy to help people
I wanted to be better and I want to help people and stuff and it's like but people just hate people do hate me though
For no reason. I haven't done anything to anybody. I wouldn't I'm a nice person like I'm a I mean
Welcome to the club psyche. You're gonna have people that are gonna disagree with certain things that you do, but
The way the way I look at it, man
My my my down I wouldn't say my downfall because there was no downfall
But my my mistake was was listening to a lot of people. That's what was my problem was
Listen to a lot of fucking he say she say shit and
Yeah, bro, that's why I say don't tell me what to do to people. I'm like, I'm like, cause people will say, Oh, mob this person, don't mob this person. Oh, you know, do this, do that. And that's what Bita was kind of like, had I started parting ways, but she was trying to help me.
end up catching a hair up your ass and y'all separate like
She literally fucking flipped on me because the shit that she had going on with J bro or not J bro J dog
And I didn't even know J dog like that. And like I said, how am I why am I gonna hate someone?
Never did nothing to me. Well, he's done this. He's done that. Well
Do this and do that but you and hear me crying about that
H.A. dog and then at the same time she has a person over there saying shit oh don't kill
don't look at his links oh here's him saying the n-word I mean it's like every like bad
thing they're they're doing and it's like well what about your mods are talking shit
about me all the time she never even cares or if anybody in the chat says something
she never never once has she said anything to anybody in the chat but she expects me
to like be timing like maybe hiding them and not have them as mods and stuff like that
And then she said, oh, you know, it's crazy.
And I was like, I just wanted to be fair at least, you know.
It's like, I don't know if it's going to be fair,
but J-Doc's not as brilliant.
I think J-Doc's sick right now.
I haven't seen him in a while.
I heard him.
Yeah, I guess he's being shy.
I haven't seen him in a while either.
Last time I think I seen him was on your panel.
And he said that, I guess, he was going through some shit
on the internet, so he was like kicking back
or some shit like that.
And it's hard.
You guys see the Lenore?
Look at Lenore's eyes.
A fucking cat's eyes is crazy.
This is like a sweet hearted cat.
Hey.
Yeah, she's beautiful cat and
There you go. I got four cats here and then people are like well oh nine cats
And I have for why do you have four cats not nine?
I was like because one year like a couple years ago one of the cats had babies
She had five babies, so I went from four to nine, but can I keep nine cats?
Okay, I mean was that is that if you have fucking ten cats
Well as long as you're fucking feeding the cats and keeping them, you know maintain it doesn't fucking matter, bro
It's not their house
The cats are not living in their fucking house, they're living in your fucking house.
They don't have to sit there and deal with it. You do.
And then Alexander said, oh well, he came to dinner and he had cat hair on his...
You know on his shirt and he and then she said this woman that has people people saying she was kicked out of the porn industry
For having a smelly vagina
She's saying I stunk and it's a but she also did like a live saying I didn't they say we both smell fine
Like after the dinner and stuff now she's saying I stink and I'm I'm I'm so ugly because that's the warning that God made me ugly
So so women would notice stay away from me and that I'm so filthy that my soul is filthy too
Not like I can't take a bath and stuff like that and clean my soul too. I don't know.
But yeah, like Lenore is an awesome cat. I'm really hurt by Alexander by the way. And it's like
she was such a fake for the as soon as we like
As soon as she parted from me, I saw her on her stream and she was drunk
Talking nonsense. And I was like, I've never seen her like drunk talking like this. And it's like
Hey, it's okay. It's okay. Do you think this cat hates me? This guy hates me. This cat this guy hates me right here
You know
This kid does not hate me. She loves me. You love me little
At the end of the day psyche, you'll you'll you'll you'll end up learning a lot of shit
Yeah, sorry. Yeah, leave me there. There's a light at the end of the tunnel, bro
I know I know everything right now is all shit right now
But you're going through a shitty fucking tunnel, but there's a fucking uh, I like the end of that tunnel, bro
Don't worry. There is I hope so
My cats I had to learn a lot of shit by myself too, bro. Believe me. I mean, I had a lot of people
warned me about a lot of things and you know what I should have listened to him because
When I thought they were against me they were actually telling me the fucking part like right because I got warned about Alexandra
I got I had people writing me privately saying
Psychi, please she's gonna do this to you for sure
Hey, she just does it to everybody and I was like, okay, and I was like well, but she was
Heavily donating. She was sending me gifts. She's sending me breakfast. She was sending me like a hundred dollar microphone through DoorDash
She was talking to me on the phone for hours. She was coming in and meeting me in person and
And so it's hard. It's hard because I was like
The love bombing sometimes does get you and in the ether and the ether which is like what con artists do
you know what I think what what a big part plays in these internet relationships, bro is that
It's hard and this is just with anyone in general. I'm not talking about anyone Pacific
But you know, it's hard to sit there and make anyone happy
Bro because you could sit there and be cool with someone and that other person that you're cool with might have a dislike for this
other person because
Those two people got a pass together
You know some people okay, well that's between y'all too sometimes you're dragged into the middle and it sucks bro because
You could tell them you could tell the truth be like look, I don't want nothing to do with this
But then you know you're taking that chance of losing a
Friendship but at the end of the day you got to ask yourself how deep was that friendship to begin?
I was like when nobody like when I felt like
Already ostracized by everybody and then she comes in and she's like the one person. She's like wow. You're smart. You're funny
You're like you're you're good at what you do
You're you're worth you're worth you're worthwhile like though like she was well one person
I was saying that and then she was
Backing it up by donating and stuff like that with nobody else. She doesn't this I'll tell you this
You know now I'm not you know saying anything, you know trying to take no one side because like I said that's between y'all two
but like
for her to go out her way and go meet up with you that shows a lot too you know
where she was at with the trust with you because you know a lot of people just
like yourself you're going through a lot of she you've probably been through a
lot of shit even be in the past bro but you know it's just some things that
we're not gonna put to understand bro and we're gonna be like I mean if you saw
that you see if you saw the dinner that night
like the smiles on our faces and the warmth.
Y'all had a good time though, right?
Y'all enjoy yourself though, right?
But also she said, I'm on my way to your house.
She's like, pick out a restaurant.
She's like, it's all gonna be on me.
She's like, don't worry.
She's like, you know, it's like,
and she knows I struggle sometimes with the finances.
And she's like, I got out taken care of,
order whatever you want off the menu.
Have as many drinks as you want.
Here, here's a joint, like smooth the joint.
Now she's saying, oh well,
I pay for the gas out there. I pay for the dinner. I pay for the drinks. He smoked my joint like
Like really I mean
like really
Look at yourself. Like alessandra. Please look at yourself
There's something wrong. There's something not right going on. Why why do you do this to people?
And I don't like how people are just
Stunning the silence by her because she puts a website with her name on it and saying, oh, you know
B to M, O, S, T, A, I'm not gonna say the rest of the name,
but yeah, you know, and then P-E-D-O-F-I-P-H-I-L-E
about people and, you know, Zayad, you know,
the rumorpedo.com, that's one of her actual websites
and stuff like that.
And I know that might appeal to you in some way too,
because, you know, you're very against,
and I am too, right?
It's like, and so it's like, okay,
we want some of these people exposed.
But then everybody goes into that category when she dumps them, you know, it's like, and then it's like, people are like, what the fuck, it really, it's just, it is, it is, I feel like the exorcist person with their head spinning around a little bit.
Like what the fuck I mean, honestly, it's like I think we all get like that at playing time
But I understand is that what you're saying, but the only person that that could honestly
Know what's really going on is you and her you know what I mean because I could see here and be like well
I can give you a why so I could say you know, well, maybe you're tripping over little shit
Maybe she's tripping over those shit, but at the end of the day, I don't know what's going on. It's not maybe it's not me
That's what I'm saying like
She does this to everybody to everybody. She does it to everybody
There's not one person if you look two years back
There's zea in her comments as her friend
right
And then it's like, now he's the devil, right?
And then it's like, there's,
there's Lala as her friend.
Now she's the devil.
And then there's, it's like every single person,
she will be friend, love bomb, send donations.
And these are people that like,
we need donations sometimes.
And this is something sometimes they're eating
because she was giving donations.
And then she flips.
We're talking about who, yes, Amber knows too.
Amber, you know exactly who I'm talking about.
I don't even need to say the name.
You too, yes, we know, we know.
And it's like, and Gotti, and all my friends too.
I brought a lot of people to her that were willing
to go and support her.
And then it's like, oh.
You're banned, you're part of that, you know, child sacrifice ring and stuff.
I mean, it's really sick.
When you get down to it, it's really sick.
It's like, she'll say the worst of the worst and stuff like that.
It's like, it's sad.
And it's the only light in the tunnel of this situation is that everyone knows now.
And I'm trying to like also bring on the information, like give her method and stuff like that and tell you what she does.
step-by-step, in detail, in detail,
because a lot of people are afraid of her.
Because they're, oh, I'm going to sue you.
Am I afraid of her suing me?
No.
I know she's running around the country hiding from lawyers and stuff like that because she doesn't want to be you know
She also has some some skeletons in the closet. I saw her in the tennis court sucking like the two white guys dig
That's why I put her in a tennis outfit on my amoeba and stuff like that. This is this lady's a porn star
Okay, this lady's a porn star with severe mental issues. Okay, and I don't need to call her out too much, but
She could be so much more and it's like even as a porn star. I don't I don't care
I don't judge her. I never judge her about that. I always thought hey
She can help people that were in trafficked and stuff like that, but now I understand why they kick her to the porn
She's trouble. She's trouble. That's it. And that's it. She kicked Godie out of her chat
She kicked DJ I'd like to have her chat then did you see the electric? Yeah, it sucks and stuff like that
You didn't know that gaudy. Yes. She is Monica Foster search on on a poor hub
We'll watch her get double double penetrated on a tennis court and stuff like that
And then she's telling us that we're bad people, you know
And I'm saying she's a bad person for doing that
But it's like how about like judge let's see not be judged and she's also being a Christian
She's saying she's a Christian does she understand Jesus?
I don't think she understands Jesus.
What did Jesus say?
Forgive, turn the other cheek, love one another,
not call everyone you mean a human trafficker
and slander them all you can until, you know,
they're just like, their reputation is dead.
I don't know, I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong and she maybe she likes you still and you don't want to lose that lose that and maybe she
Because she I do hear her talking nicely about you and I don't want to turn against you next and say
accusations against you
I mean at the end of the day psyche everyone has their own, you know thing going on with certain people
I mean you don't sit there and tell me about my beliefs. I have a certain people
I'm gonna ever but I would I ever in a million years do that like what am I ever in a million years?
But that's her
thing. Her thing is like, oh, let me gather information, find all the sensitivities, find
all the weakest points, find all the friends, then turn everyone against them, and say the
opposite of what they are. I don't know. She's evil. I don't know how to say it. She's calling
me evil. She's saying I worship a child-killing demon and stuff like that, which is not true.
It's like lady look at yourself. You have serious serious problems. I'm not trying to diagnose you
I'm not a psychiatrist or anything, but lady
The ability to be
Passing as a normal person and have your mind your mind is sick
Your mind is sick lady. Okay. I'm sorry
Alexandra, you're sick. Okay
You need you need some help not anybody not everybody else not zaya not pebs not me not gaudi not tg
Electra amber you you and I'm the first person
Well, I take that back Zaya and pebs do need help maybe maybe they do but it's like
Maybe they do but maybe because of her. Maybe I don't I don't know. I don't know the
Look at yourself lady. Look at yourself first. Okay. I don't care if I have like thousand lives made about me
You know how I'm like some kind of you know demon worshiping child sacrificing pervert and stuff like that. Okay. Look at yourself lady, okay?
You have problems you have problems you need to examine yourself stop pointing at everybody else stop calling everyone a human trafficker
So I'm calling everyone a spiritual trafficker. So I'm coming everyone else a pervert
Look at yourself. You're a porn star that turned into like a streamer. Okay, you're not some special angel
I mean Jesus Christ
What the fuck is wrong with you lady? What the fuck is wrong with you? I'm gonna stand up for these
Jesus Christ Jesus Christ
Mr.. Slave just a Christ
Alexandra, why are you so crazy?
Alexandra what are you doing? I mean you're a little bit loony tunes, okay?
Jesus Christ lady, I don't care how much money you have. I don't care how scared you are go run around the country
Hiding from everybody from from lawsuits and stuff. You're not gonna sue anybody. Don't be scared of this lady
She wants everyone be scared of her intimidated. She's a black lady. You can't say the n-word. You can't say this
Say whatever you want. Yeah
She's not she's not so scary as you think she's not as scary as you think, okay?
And I'm the only one that says her name right. I say Alexandra. That's her name
Alexandria
I'm the only one that says her name right. I don't care if you never talk to me and lady. Okay?
I don't want to be your friend anymore. Okay, you're a phony. You're phony fraudulent. You're the fraudulent porn star turned
Not so popular streamer. I brought I brought you clout. Okay. You didn't bring me shit
All you brought me was a bunch of headaches and sadness and misery and sadness as all it was
You suck bitch. That's it
Go fucking suck some more white cocks you whore
By the way, we do have the same birthday. I do understand her on a level that some people don't but she's watching right now
Hey, how about you and her got the same birthday exact same birthday two years?
Yeah, I
Did not know that. Yeah, we do is why I understand here. I understand the capricorn
I also made a video of her. Do you ever see the video I made of her?
Nice one. I want to show you this. I want to show everyone this because while she's making AI of me with my cats stealing
Robin banks and stuff. I made a video of her. She said she loved it. Okay, I'll play it. Okay. Oh, I got it
Oh, I you say your cash with Robin banks
Well, that's what she made the beam of the first time when I asked her if you're gonna get me
It was me sleeping kind of dirty on the couch
Like with the cats with bags of money on top of them
I might do so this is a song she uses with her favorite song and it was her favorite song that I made and
Then she said well, can you well? I didn't she didn't ask me, but I was like I just made her this video
This is actually the most expensive
Things in the AI that I do this this program. We're really okay, and I tried really hard to make it sure
I mean defeat her feet are white and stuff like that, but this is her face
This is her this is the beat so when she's saying I was like so insulting to her and stuff like this
this is how much I thought of her at the time and I'm finding it right now and
One of my favorite videos too. One of my favorite songs here is her favorite song
She loved it and she did a whole show about how I'm so great AI now
She says oh, I'm this even AI to manipulate people. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, but
I made this with pure love in my heart.
She loves it, she did a whole,
she deleted everything nice,
nice that she didn't give me a whole three-part interview
when nobody else was fucking with me.
Like really, like she came in, she saw me hurt,
she saw me injured, but it was really just to get back
at Bita, like she just, cause she hated Bita.
And then it's like when she saw me
just even go and beat this channel.
Like that was what really turned her against me and stuff, but yeah, I'm finding it so this yeah
I'll show you the video. It's a short video. It's not a short video
It's like actually like three minutes long, but it's a short music video and one of my best videos
And it's called watch me ascend and you can see
how
Highly I regarded her. Okay. It was it was this is not anything and it's not anything insulting
She likes this. I she can't and I also made a neon priestess and stuff like that. I had to go down a little further
I've been a lot of videos in the past four months
This is the good guys. We were friends for a good six months before she turned on me
I didn't see the other side of her
You know, okay here that I found it and I hope you guys enjoy this and if she ever says I never loved her
Who would make a video like this about someone they never loved that's
That's my question. Here we go. I'm gonna post it right now. Here we go. Share. Okay. Got it. Here we go
Enjoy
it refines my mirror eyes they don't flinch in the storm they just watch the illusions form
i cut through the nerves which planes mid-flight bleeding truth in the glare of the light now
i'm electric wide open the light didn't gauge the feeling let it thrive watch me ascend while i'm
Sushi
Bless in the dark, praise in the blue The night is the canvas where visions move
My voice cracks under, my veins rumble Hold me close, I'm becoming new
I was close, I fell through cosmic time
Madness and magic, you're pulsing mine
Circle diva-
been a sin. But I also have, before that, it's not quite her. I'll say it was inspired by her.
It's called Panther Lope. And just imagine, this is me singing the song, and it's her
as the femme fatale or whatever this is. It's called Panther Lope. One more, and then I'll
I think it's the most unique song. Hold on here it is right here
I'll skip panther eyes cutting through the smoke of green sharp as a terrible
I step from the heat like a nightmare that
Thought I was sweet but sweetness is a snare for me
Your lips with myth and motion
Your fingers brushing only dust and your own delusions
Do you want me?
my fucking mind that's fucking AI like the lyrics and shit that shit is crazy
i'm not bad at it i'm not bad at it you're not you gotta admit i i it's more than just
oh let this make the i mean it's like it doesn't make it hard bro i don't give a fuck how anyone
says it oh it's AI yeah no that's art bro like no one can not anyone could just do that shit like
Yeah, thank you. Thank you. I appreciate that a lot
Might as it might as dry. Yeah. Well, I don't know that I don't know Goddy, but uh, that was uh, I
Made that before me anything else and that was prophetic. I think and I'm not a bad psychic
You know, you can say I'm a bad psychic or whatever who has the right to say what gifts I have from God
You know who who has but who is she to say God gave this to you God? Is she God?
No, no lady
No, no, you're not God
It's between me and God not between you and me okay, it's between me and God and you don't have any
Right to intrude in the relationship between God and I okay?
Nothing nothing you can't say anything
That's why she's shutting up now.
She's shutting up now.
And you know she made the Mexican cartel.
She said I'm doing magic for the Mexican cartel, right?
You saw the whole, the cartels and the...
You saw that, right?
She said, she said, oh, he's working for the Mexican mafia.
Doing magic for them, but he's not a good magician.
Hey, I'm the best magician you ever met, bitch, okay?
Okay, lady, best one you ever met.
You want me one better, okay?
You mess with the wrong and I gga. Okay. That's what I have to say to you mess with the wrong nigga
Straight to pop verse right there drop
Sorry, sorry mess with the wrong one because everyone else is gonna be scared to go go run in their holes
Be afraid of you lady. I'm not afraid of you lady. I am not fucking afraid of you
Okay, Monica Foster. No
Let's go watch everyone and go search on porn hub go watch her take two dicks on the tennis court
Okay, and then take what she says seriously
That's what I gotta say
Sorry
Now you're good at your panel row good get it off your chest man. Oh, I mean I got it. I got have to it's like too much
too much
it's like
I know people are going to be scared.
People get scared?
I don't get scared.
Do I care if I die?
No, I really don't.
I'm not afraid of death,
because I know I go on forever.
Other people will be afraid of,
oh, my reputation, whatever.
My reputation's already as bad as it can get.
And still, I have 32 people in my chat.
Go talk to the two people in your chat. It's still it's okay, bro. You have to say lady, okay?
Okay lady
That's all I have to say I got off my chest here we go
I don't I don't really use the heart I use it last night on Sam and he deserves it. He has a hard R. He's a hard R
I mean, you, him calling that is like a, a, a compliment, bro.
Yeah, I should compliment him.
He is, yeah, he, he wishes he would.
He wishes, yeah.
He's still working his way up to the hard art person.
Yeah.
He wishes.
He's beating in him, burning me in a dumpster.
I'm a phoenix. I'm a phoenix. I don't burn in a dumpster. I ride
I rise as a fucking you rise out that motherfucker. Yeah, I fly out as a fucking bird and I shit all over them
Ain't the phoenix the one that comes out like the the bird of fire though. Yeah
Every 300 years the phoenix makes a nest the nest is on fire the phoenix burns
But it's a spirit and so everything all the physical it just burns away and it comes out as a spiritual being and then it
starts again
Reborn you will speak. Okay. Okay. Maybe I'm saying too much. I said too much, right?
Hey, can someone else come on the panel if someone else comes on the panel within a couple next couple minutes with clumsy and I I
Probably just wrap it up because I probably did say too much
Phoenix does rise Phoenix does rise and I know about the Phoenix, right?
But come on, since can someone come up and just talk,
cause, hey, no, no, so Aaron doesn't want to.
Hey, we still have 25 people in chat.
Hey, someone come up here and chat with us.
And if not, I'll wrap it up in a couple of minutes.
But if you wanna like continue the conversation,
I will continue the conversation.
And Monica Foster, come on up.
Let's have it, let's have it out.
Let's have it out.
Because after you said oh bother me because I said no contact just like all these other bitches do oh
Always harass me talking. You all came to my chat and on my panel after you said that so you're just much of hypocrites, okay?
This is hypocritical, you know what God says about hypocrites
Not good things, okay?
Sorry, no true. Sorry, not sorry
Yep, you know hypocrites thieves
Stoops dealers of the soul
Deceivers the severs. Yes, exactly
They they wait like a lion outside your front door
for your weakness
Wait how it's on you. Yeah, exactly
of the
And so this is g24th. Okay, so sacred language of birthdays g24th. Okay. Let me see. I got it right here
the
Okay, so g24th secret language
Let me see if I got it let me see take your time. Okay, I got it. Just give me a second. Okay
Okay, so June 24th, your birthday is called
the day of the blissful wizard, June 24th, correct?
The day of the blissful wizard, those born on June 24th are often completely taken up
with their vocation or art or their business concern.
The more highly evolved individuals born in the state of both themselves to creative,
positive projects, the less highly evolved, contribute their energies to undertaking with
the decidedly negative or destructive cast.
Both are equally involved, particularly in a technical sense, since June 24th people
their activities down to the last detail. Technique for these individuals is not so much an objective
study which can be learned by everyone, but rather a highly personal set of tools
which allows them to express themselves unhindered and master what they do.
Usually, the more highly-evolved individuals born in the state are attracted to spiritual
pursuits which they see as manifesting divine love.
Those on the path, this ultimate goal, cultivate kindness, awareness, sensitivity, psychic
abilities, religious fervor, and respect for all living things.
Poorly-evolved individuals are, of course, in the opposite direction, preferring conflict,
It is unlikely, but not impossible, for the less highly evolved can turn their values around in a
single lifetime. But since many of them are now granted a lifespan in excess of 84 years, one
year in a cycle, in a sense, more than one lifetime can be lived, offering opportunity
for tremendous change. This change can come about through study, increased self-awareness,
the basic desire to improve oneself.
June 24th people have what can be described
as religious fervor for their principal activity.
They strive for self discipline
and are capable of tremendous feats of concentration.
They value a flowing, natural, spontaneous,
somewhat improvised work method
and one backed by an ironclad technical skills.
Even around June 24th, people come aware
that their work holds great potential
good and bad ends. Those born in the state often encounter a severe midlife crisis in their early
40s concerning their ethics. Above all June 24 people want to be left alone to do what they love
most and therefore their family and friends must be highly understanding of the strict privacy
they need for their work. Occasionally they those born in the state venture out to perform a high
Important work and the confines of their safe often secret home base
Those 224 people who work in offices or primarily out in society usually value their home life
More than their work and reserve the larger part of their energies for personal interests. That's your that's your
Bro, that's crazy
Aaron here. There's Aaron. Yeah, you like that one. That is crazy. What's up, Aaron? What's cracking?
Hey, Clemsey.
How you doing?
I'm going to get up here and explain himself.
Hi, Psyche.
Hi, sweetheart.
How are you?
I love you.
I love you too.
Good.
Okay.
Go ahead.
No.
Continue.
But do you have a message to send out?
I have an important message to send out.
Whatever you're going to say is important.
I don't want to interrupt.
I'm sorry.
No, the important message was just Gotti's trying to quell my voice
Gotti, you know quelling of voices. Yeah, there's even no quelling of Aaron's voice. Do you see Lenore? Look at Lenore's eyes
Finally, where have you been Lenore?
It's something about it's something about Lenore's eyes, but I don't know what the fuck it is
Everyone's like oh a black cat has eyes like that. No, I don't know what it is
No, Lenore knows things. He's special. She's special. She's that cat is so beautiful, bro. Thank you
God is here. First of all, I would never try to call your voice. Okay
Unquellable voice your voice can never be well. I would never try to even call your voice. What are you talking about?
You're telling me to crawl it in the side chat. I never said well. I've said that
Don't tell me lies that I never told
You're always speaking fucking riddles, you know, I'm sick of that shit. I
Can clearly state your fucking problem, please
Am I right clumsy am I right on my fucking wrong? Well, what's going on?
Motherfucker, you just took a piss. What the fuck is wrong with you, man?
I'm drinking motherfucker.
Fucking bladder infection, motherfucker.
Snicker taking pisses every five fucking five minutes, man. What the fuck?
Yeah, this is a P2.
He went again. Motherfucker, you didn't wash your hands. You didn't wash your fucking hands.
I didn't. I didn't. I'm sorry.
You fucking dirty ass motherfuckers. All you people are fucking dirty.
Fuck, Aaron. Aaron, you better wash your fucking hands, bitch.
Oh, come on. Hey
What do you mean? What do you mean? Come on? What do you mean? Come on? I'm a bitch. She just called me
She just said I was quelling her. I don't quell fucking people. All right
I
Believe in freedom of speech
No, I'm being quelled. I am being quelled. Not being quelled continue stop quelling me gaudi. Oh shit
Go quell yourself
How are you?
I'm good. I'm kind of good. Yeah, I'm good.
I'm good.
I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
Shit.
Shit. I'm fucking fine.
I'm the best.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Right. Yep. Uh-huh.
I'm the best.
Did you get my message?
Yeah. Loud and clear.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
No, I'm not gonna wear that suit. I'm not gonna wear the bunny suit. No, I'm not gonna wear that bunny suit
Why what's wrong with the bunny suit?
I don't want to wear it. It's yellow.
Yellow bunny suit. I'm not wearing a yellow bunny suit, okay?
Yellow?
Want the black
Are you kidding me yellow bunny suit? And why is there like a flap in the ass?
Flap flap in the ass
It's not yellow
That's even worse fuck that shit
The clumsy way that shit. I'm not wearing that shit. Well, I'd rather have him working Cowboys jerseys. That's all I'm saying
Here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, war, it's war, it's war, it's war, it's war, it's war, it's war, it's war, it's war, it's war.
Oh, shake, shake, shake the cat, shake the cat, shake the pussy, shake the pussy, shake the pussy, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it off, shake it off, shake it off, shake it off, shake it off, shake it off, shake it off, shake it off, shake it off.
The fuck he takes a piss and he fucking wipes his hands on the cat he wipes his fucking hands on the cat this guy
No wonder nobody watches the channel anymore dirty
You know, I love you Jamie
But we can all get it. You know get off. Oh, I have a video to show you guys
Hold on one second. You know, you like this out and shake it off. I think you left. You're here to shake it off song
It's okay. It's okay. Shake it off. University Taylor Swift shake it off. I have a song.
This is the shake it off parody. Did I got it right? Here we go. Hold on a second. We
got it right here. Here we go. Oh, I got it.
I'm richer than Bruce Wayne
My life is so great
I just can't keep a date
But it's not enough for me
To equate a country
I need more love than a claim
Cause I am insane
I'll make pop music
That's triplet and useless
And use my
To expand my fan base to a bigger size
Yes this song is really lame, lame, lame, lame, lame, lame
And this video's the same, same, same, same, same, same
I'm the structure-leading twerking and ballet
Make it stop, make it stop
You like y'all, yeah, it's my style
I like my dress like an urban air
I am cool as who I am, am I?
I'm always surprised
You care way too much
I just want the whole world to love Tay-Tay
That's why I'm just really trying to relate
To every race that you sing of all these ways
Make it stop, make it stop
I have absolutely no rhythm, it's sad
When I dance and look like a paralyzed rat
Hypnotizing you in half so that you can
Turn it off, turn it off
Don't you find it sad, sad?
I look on, now they creep, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country, you go back to country
This is where you belong girl, you ain't never leave it!
Now play that country music, devil woman!
Yo guys, thanks for watching my Shake It Off parody.
If you want to see the rest of my parodies, click this box right here.
Wow. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. What the fuck was that? I I don't know. I don't know. What was that? I thought it was Cheyna Swift at first. What the fuck was that? It was, but she's a man. Baby. She's a man, baby.
No, I'm not seeing another side of Taylor's with when she was at the fucking Super Bowl shit
That bro was slamming all kinds of fucking beer doing shots
All that shit for nothing in her fucking man's team lost goddamn. That was funny
Have you ever seen you ever seen and new and Humm-la-Bay is
Sadie
He was under the church of Satan, but he had a daughter named Zina. I just want to show you what Zina looks like real quick
There she is right here and what do you think of this? Oh
It's Taylor Swift
Well, okay. No, that's that one lady
She was the mom on Liar Liar the one that was suing
For custody I think
Everyone else. Oh the old movie Liar Liar, huh?
There you go with Jim Carrey, right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah when it was mean to her kids
The Witch, Goddy Goddy, 2020, Aaron, 9 and 9.
Hey guys, you know how much I love you?
Here's how much I love you.
Oh, he's up on the cross living this.
Holy shit.
I have to fashion yourself for you, huh?
I will.
There you go.
I'll do it, I'll do it because I love you guys so much.
I really do.
And we love you and I have to say I am so happy that you left your hair down again
I get you like this hair style so much better so much better. I hate the man bun so much
Man bun I mean it's like okay, and so he does it and so he does it
What I say anything yeah, you like it. Yeah, okay, whoa
I'm fine. You know Aaron. I'm clumsy. You know Aaron. Yeah. Mm-hmm. Yeah
Erin's awesome. Erin is awesome. She is. Thank you. Thank you.
I'll do a clumsy song if he wants one. I will do it. You still haven't made mine. I'm not talking to you.
Yeah, okay. Okay. Well, we'll talk on. Yeah, don't make mine. She make hers, okay? Yeah.
I will.
I guess technically you can go ahead and make clumsy his song, but I get my video before
he does.
I know.
Where's McQueen tonight?
I don't know.
Where's everyone?
There's people that should be here.
Someone went to the bathroom.
I didn't make a song thing I call Moving On.
I'll play it real quick.
This is called Moving On, guys.
My latest hit.
I'm moving on up
Along in the ashes
Talking to the ghost so I went wrong
Held on a hurt like it could save me
But all it did was make the night too long
I gave my faith to the faithless
I let some wolves get close enough to bite
The truth survives and hands will try to break it
And mornin' always pulls us out from the night
Now I can feel the way begin to fall
I'll not drag the darkness with me
I survived it all, I survived it all
Like, I'm done. Goodbye. No more drama?
Well, it's kind of like I'm moving on from a lot of it.
Moving on. I'm over it.
I'm over the fighting and stuff, and I'll move on.
I'll move on.
We all got to move on sometimes, you know?
Yeah.
You're muted. You're muted, clumsy. You're muted.
We need the old psyche back when you see the tarot readings, bro. People come up and enjoy their self and
You know what I mean?
Yeah, and I'm still here, but what I do see that tarot is like if you ask me
I'll give you a reading. I'm not gonna like say I'm gonna give you a reading and like
For someone who doesn't want it, you know, because I have enough people like here
Trying to play with my mind and stuff like that. If you really want one, I will do I'm happy to do that
But I'm not I don't force it on people
I don't you've been pushing his tarot on me. It's been pushed upon me. I
Know exactly. I really don't I don't want to push it on anybody and because it is an art
I when I was eight years old
My sister would go to do ice skating and she would do ice skating and stuff
I'd be at the mall and I go to the bookstore
It's called Brentanos bookstore and that's when I got my first couple decks from Brentanos and
But and then I would read for my mom and I had the book when I was my mom and mom would be like
You have to read without the book you have to I don't care what you do in life
Just be the best of what you are
Yeah
And so, and they didn't care.
Yeah, go ahead.
Moms knows best, bro.
She does, yeah.
My mom knows, my mom's a very smart lady.
My mom's a great lady.
And it's like,
Maybe for guys, she is.
To see like her docs and stuff like that, it hurts.
And, you know, and there are people with docs
and it's like, they don't deserve that.
And it's like, I'll leave if that starts happening.
But,
You know my family loves me. I love my family. I would do it. I
I'm a great family. Are we thinking about my family doing it. You want to find an army?
You know, I have like like 50 people. I have like, you know, 20 nieces and nephews
15 like brothers, I mean, I just have a huge family
You know, you want to fight against the army? Don't don't allow these people to suck
something out of you though bro that you built so hard in the past years and
that what I'm saying is yourself that that's I understand it's everyone's
human bro everyone's gonna react to a certain thing you know controversy does
sell no matter how you look at it money-wise streaming what whatever the
To suck everything out of you psyche because on some real shit. I wouldn't be here, bro
If I didn't think you were all right, dude, you know what I mean? I know I know
People will sit there and call me. Oh, you're on a game and bro. I don't give a fuck
Psychies cool as fuck like me and psyche had our deal theme back in the day, but it's always banter little banter shit and
people just try to sit there and put people in these categories like well
This is the group of people with this and this and this and this is a group of people with this and this and this
This is the group within what's your group then you get what I'm saying at the end of the day
I think what it is and with myself, too. I think we just need to learn just to
They're gonna talk shit no matter what we're gonna have to just move on
So protected
I wouldn't go on, but I know I'm protected. I know my family's protected. Everyone's different. Yeah, everyone's different
I'm not gonna see
There's people that just made you afraid. That's what the way doing a fear and when you're like, oh
I can't do it anymore because I'm I'm so afraid. I
Know we have like a big circle of light protecting all of us
And so I can go on and I can like not only go on
I can fight back and I will fight back because there's some people that are afraid to fight back about it
And it's like I'll stick it for Amber. I'll stick up for even Zaya. I'll stick up for the end of the day
I don't even know this person see
Amber is a wrench her name is a wrench in the chat
Yeah, everyone
I did want to ask you one thing. Yes
Do you enjoy doing tarot?
It's my as a patch is it's my passion. It's like it's it's like well
I don't need I don't need cards basically and everyone will say oh he needs cards and blah blah blah and it's like
Fraud and psychic fraudulent person the cards are like
basically
Like a like a storyline and that I can go off of
To just not because I have so many voices coming in my head at once right I am a psychic and no one can tell me
I don't have these spiritual gifts. I know
That's not what I was getting to I was just getting to the point of
Do you enjoy doing it? Do you enjoy being who you are and if you said yes, I do I enjoy tarot
I enjoy talking to people. I enjoy who I am exactly
I know yeah, and I am I am me. What's the ashes of sun? I am me and I don't care what anyone says
I am me. I am just me
If you look back on your old videos, bro, when you first came around
Look how it take this how you want. I don't mean this in a bad way
But look how alive that you look back in the day, bro. Look how
You've looked a lot more and right
But you you you you're you're whole
And I'm gonna say I was happier I was happier and
but of the same time I was being hurt constantly I was being
Constantly my heart was being
stabbed in
when I was just like so open and so nice.
We'll take advantage of shit like that, psych.
Yeah, people take advantage of shit like that.
So maybe I'm like a little bit saltier,
like a little bit more salt with the sugar.
There's no, like, because it was just like,
there's a lot of sugar back then.
It was a lot of like innocence.
And I watched back and I say,
I was innocent and I was just loving and whatever anyone said, I would ignore things.
But I had to get to the point where it's like my defender came out.
My defender came out and it's like the defender sometimes takes precedence over my sweet self.
My sweet self is still there.
No, you're not gonna destroy this person this because you can because I'm very easily destroyed
I mean, it's very easy, but it's like I'm not gonna let myself be destroyed
I'm gonna fight cuz I'm a fighter too. I'm a fight
You're the type of you're gonna fucking take me down completely. I'm gonna take you down with me
You know what I mean? Like that typo, but the thing about it good
I
House with me, but I don't I don't want to hurt anybody or I don't want to but I I mean like I
I do have the power to I see a lot that I don't say
I mean, I feel a lot. I see a lot. I I could but I'm not the kind of a person
I don't want to hurt anybody
I just want you happy again.
I want you happy.
I'm almost back there.
It's like, that's what part of the moving on is.
I'm just going to let people go their own way.
and stop trying, stop trying to,
for acceptance, we'll, we'll never get.
But the thing, Psyche, don't, don't, don't think you,
we were, people are telling you to change overnight, bro.
This shit does take time, especially,
I'm not gonna say you're a hole that you dug yourself,
but a hole that you were pretty much placed in.
You have to dig yourself out of that hole.
All right, and you know what?
I'm a Capricorn, I can, you know,
if you ever see a goat, where they climb,
you climb up the steep cliff.
You ever see that?
Stupid shit, bro, I'm gonna be licking the fucking salt on the fucking mountains, bro. And they'll literally
Put their life on the line for that. That's weird. I don't know what it's called
They will but they can't they can do it
Define physics. Yeah
A capricorn anytime they set their mind to something absolutely it will get them
Yeah, I don't give up if I fall down if I get like a ego picks me up and throws me in the in the in the hell
I'll still keep climbing out of it and get to the top of it
I just I just don't stop
That's about me chains chains baby chains
You put in those chains on yourself making yourself have to work twice as hard
Sometimes I do you're you're so right. I mean it's like when people see it and it's like but all I can do
It's just keep one. It's a one step at a time. I'll take and I can go pretty fast taking the one step
Where it's like other others would fall immediately and I can keep going and look I'm still here. I'm still here
Despite it all. I am. Hey
We're all special we're all special all of us have our special our special
Gift from God that will take us out of this and I have and I'm gonna take my gift
And I'm gonna take as far as I can go if I if I go
Hey, I had this guy. I love this guy
Danny, you know and
I'm we're sitting there one day and he's like, you know, I don't care if people call me gay because I'm your friend
He's like, I don't care if people call me gay for pay, you know the next day
He gets shot in the chest times at a gas station and it's like
Yeah, that was my friend Danny. I don't know if you were there when I was promoting him and stuff
A couple weeks ago. I was like ever go to his chat. He had a biggest smile on his face
He said about time. He's about time. He's like, I'm gonna give you a if I get a hundred people my chat
I'm gonna give you a kiss. He got about 40 people so I never got the kiss
He was a good hearted person. He didn't deserve to like go to the gas station get shot three times in the chest
And then be gone and stuff like that
I do believe in like a higher
Maybe he had a sole contract that said that would happen and stuff like that. I can't question God about these things, but
I do think things happen for a reason.
I do believe that our souls do go on.
I don't think that this meat suit that last 100 years
is like our entire nice fan.
I think we go on and I just think,
hopefully goes to a better place, you know?
Well, okay.
I need you to read Midnight's thing
about stop trying to make friends.
I know. I mean, I mean, that's wise. I mean, that's a wise, she's a wise lady. She has cat Williams. I don't, she's, I think maybe she's a blackly and I'm sorry if I said the N word last night, several times, I'll be this channel to people because I was angry and hurt and lashing out.
And it's like, it's not like any, it's not anything against anybody of any race or anything. I'm not racist.
I mean, people might say they're like,
well, honestly, this is the first time I ever hear you
about you crashing out with the N-word like that.
Right.
But I have before, and I even said it
when I was in the Black channels,
I was on the beef sector or the Mo3 sector,
and I said the N-word, and that was like a scandal there.
But.
So you know what the mode three-second the black sector to that's
Blaze bro, that's where I started I started in the I started in the trenches
The worst place the hardest place to start for a white person basically I started there
That's where I started
Yeah, there's a lot of brothers and sisters over there. Yeah, for sure. Yeah, yeah. And they're cool. They're really cool. And I'm still friends with some of them.
I totally fucking adore you, man.
I started with a good pussy show this one called the good pussy show
And that was my first channel I was on I did black jeopardy and I lost I'm black jeopardy
I but I still got a few points on it, you know, but I was on black jeopardy and they're like
Who the fuck is this honking? Yeah, people play dirty though. This honky
So this right here shouldn't be any any surprises
It's not it's not it's easy compared to that and it really is I mean that's why I'm still here if it was like hard
They docks over there, and they don't give off. Well, I know and so the docks in here is like nothing
It's like it's like it's a part of the wind. It's like nothing
is like nothing compared to what I was doing.
I didn't know you came from that community.
I didn't know that.
I was like first community, I was on live panels
on the Mothry sector.
Okay, so you got some experience a little bit
like dealing with these troll communities in a way then.
Right, I mean, that's why I can deal with it.
Seriously, I would have not be here still
because I would be like...
In shock or like, you know, not able to continue but I started there the hardest
I started the hardest places and
Thank you to be honest, bro. If you've been through that, bro, then this shit right here is this shit
It's a laugh it's a laugh
It is it is at the end of the day, but you know, we as as for myself
I could take shit a little overboard too, you know what I mean? We all do
We all do, but
Don't ever go overboard I'm innocent of all charges 2020 said right
I've accusations charges
I want to be in jail. I want to be like, you know, put through a trial. I want to I want to I just don't want to like
Just like that be the narrative of like that's who I am like no
It's like unless I'm in jail and that's I'm like accused of something specific. I just there's all these random
Tenuous things acute. I'm a huge sub and so I just laugh at it because it's like if I was not
Really that wasn't if I was if I did something I should be in prison if I did
These these these communities expect people like
Newbies or you know people that are new to their communities to come and oh well
My real name is so and so and so and so and so and so in my past this and this and this and this and this
You don't work like that on the internet
Yeah, so when they do find out she and then they're like, well, why didn't you say so well you think people are just gonna come on here and just
Flat out like the way I look at it, bro
As long as you're not some kind of fucking super fucking weirdo and it's
validating on paperwork like
I mean, everywhere, everywhere.
Right, I mean, there's a weirdo, maybe a weirdo, maybe a weirdo, and a weirdo in certain ways.
Yeah, but weirdos can be with other weirdos.
We're all weirdos in a way.
In a way.
If you get around your trash weirdos, and hateful weirdos.
I have every thought and every horrible thought
you could imagine and go through my mind.
I've been through, before I came on this panel,
before I came on this stream,
I was having these like intrusive thoughts
and things like that, right?
I mean, it's like, just having the thought,
you feel guilty, right?
Is even having thoughts or imagination and stuff.
But then I realized, I can think anything
and it's like, that's just,
Ether that's just like this is a smoke. It's nothing. It's nothing
I'm not gonna like be held down and you call it something because of this ether
Because of what's in the ether and stuff like that. I know who I am
But behind it all behind all the smoke and everything there is a heart that no one's gonna touch
And it's like, am I gonna hate anybody at the end of the day?
No, am I gonna blame anybody?
Am I gonna really go after anybody
and try to hurt anybody?
No, I have a loving heart.
Like, after all this, I still have a loving heart.
That's all I'm really wanting to project
is my loving heart.
And it's like, I don't want that to-
That's it, that's pretty much all we have.
On anybody-
Just perfecting-
On anybody, nobody.
Yeah.
Worst person we all have intrusive thoughts. Believe me. I'd be in jail 76 times over if I acted on him
Right, we watch putting something out in the universe as
Something bad against somebody. No, I don't do that. We watch and she's got it all day
Right, there's movies we watch where people are killed and stuff like that is and we can we can see in like in a
Dorphin rush
Seeing people killed and we do all this stuff like that and it's like
You know our murderer no it doesn't because this is just in our mind
Do you know how many women watch true life documentaries about life movies, lifetime movies and the true crime?
No, no, no, not the lifetime movies.
I'll be questioning my wife sometimes when she watches. I'm like, what are you, what are you trying to do?
Yeah, exactly. We're looking for people.
What is it? What is it? Life is hard.
She's like, did you know to get rid of this? I'm like, what the fuck? What did you say to me?
We're telling them how they did wrong. Let's see. You shouldn't have done it that way. Here's what you should have done
I'm taking you out eat tonight. And yeah
I love you
It's really bad like hey look at like it's still here. I don't have those 24 people
There's two people in the chat. I don't care. I don't I'm just I am happy. I am happy
The most part and I'm gonna stop chasing
chasing rainbows or some chasing like the you know certain people it takes time
psyche we don't expect you to change overnight bro and I'm not perfect I'm
the most imperfect person you can imagine perfect either I still say some
fucking crazy ass shit sometimes I think that's not
Is it whatever you do is like really matters, right? It's like whatever you do. I'll tell you this though
I just won't attack someone that doesn't deserve it. I'll tell you that but if they
I don't think I deserved it like you know what I get I don't think I did anything
That can't be forgiven
but
I'm willing to
I understand
People are now we're in a realm that Aaron doesn't know
Because half of the shit, like I wasn't joking when I was talking the other night, I think
it was a clumsy, that 99% of the stuff that goes on, I have no idea.
I don't know backstory.
I don't know history.
I just tend to, you know, if I like hanging around with you, I like hanging out with you.
That's it. Look at the cats home. Look at the cats right there. Lenora is sitting next to Lola and they're both fine
Lenora is agreeing with me. Yes. Yeah, she's nodding. She's next to Lola and Lola is not
There's tricks right there too. You see Trace?
What the fuck is this? Lola is his mom, but but Lenora's sitting there up with Lola and
another friend. Rudy?
Rudy? He's right here. There's Rudy right there.
There you go, man. Yeah, he's right there.
He's sitting there too. Damn cat, so comfortable, bro. That's their spot. Yeah, this is, they all,
today it was so sweet. They're all just around me or jumping on me when, yeah.
Midnight, god damn it.
Gosh, I'm gonna run over cats and then you have one up. It's okay. It's okay. Hey, my cats are my they're my babies in my life
Okay, I can't
Really and that is perfectly fine. That's the thing do stuff that makes you happy you love your cats
You love Cheryl do that stuff and surround yourself with good people that make you feel good about yourself
I always poke my nose back and say hey, are you still mad?
It's like people that will never forgive me for no reason, you know, why are you chasing them?
That's what I'm saying. It's like I'm gonna stop doing that. It's like I'm but it is learning
It is a learning process, right?
It is.
It is, it is.
I totally understand.
That's why I just step in and out of panels
every once in a while.
Yeah, it's a hard it's a hard community Aaron. It's Aaron. It's a hard community. It's
Tough it's tough midnight. I want you to be my friend
Midnight, are you my friend midnight? Can you give me a thumbs up if you're my friend midnight or do you hate me?
I want to see you get a cup of coffee and laugh at the ups
Give me a thumbs down if if you'll never never fuck with me, but give me a thumbs up if I if I hey
I'm not a bad guy. I don't think I'm a bad guy
Well, from what I know of you know, you're not and you have just gotten so off of
Tarot and so angry that I'm like
Wait angry because I it's just hurt. It's hurt. It's hurt. It's like
My heart being stabbed stabbed it and it's like then the heart bleeds and it's like
It hurts sometimes it does hurt like being called out of my name
I'll all the it's it's not fair. It's not us, but it's okay. It's okay. I know it goes
But I was going doing me. I love you
What midnight said was
We really held it when you wait no, I do like you, but what where'd it go? Oh
She's gonna talk shit. Yeah, she said she does like you but she is gonna talk shit, which is okay. I mean, it's like
If I had fun with you because see that's my whole goal as far as going to panels and chats and stuff
Is somebody will play back with me like midnight when I said I can get you a buffet ticket for the strip club and
She you know teased me back. That was great. I loved it. That's what I look for you look for tarot and cats
That's your people. It's still me like down there buried deep inside of all this other shit that's going on
like that's
My heart and it's like that but but if you but I do you have to guard my heart a little bit because
Yes, you know people just want to like
Drink it. Yeah, but you're doing you're doing
Livestreams so with me it's different. You know, I just go on live streams go on the panels
And I can always jump off and say okay. I'm done and then not see anybody for two weeks
But with you you're you're doing the paneling yourself
So, you have these people come in that are mean or hateful or try to troll you entirely
too hard and I'm talking to nobody.
Psyche's crashed, clumsy's gone.
At the end of the day, at the end of the day.
I'm showing my face, I'm showing my life,
I show my floor, I show my dirty house.
It's dirty sometimes, sometimes it's clean.
You know, I show everything and it's like,
okay, they can jump on that, but it's like,
I'm showing it.
Who are these people that are like jumping on me?
They're like avatars.
They're like, I don't know who they are.
I show everything, you know, I'm me.
I show-
You're unapologetically you.
Yeah, and if you don't like it
You don't have to be here and it's like, you know, I want people to be here to fuck with me that in a good way
You know, yeah, that's just what midnight said, you know that they'll fuck with you
But it's like a good kind of fun with you
It's like I understand initiation I understand hazing but it's
Over a year like a year and a half and so the hazing is done. The hazing should have ended some time
I should have some time ago. Yes, but some people I
Can never we know and it's okay
It's okay, you know, but
Yeah, I love you. I love you Amber. I love you. I love you Aaron. I love you
Clumsy, I mean, I love you Jamie. I love you Joni. I mean, I love you Gotti
There's so many people that are so good to me like they're just
If I like there's so many people at the last minute so many
hundreds at probably over
hundreds of times
Someone came through the last minute if I need if I really need something and so I'm sorry
I'm sorry if I did anything wrong to anybody or if I was like, you know made fun of somebody or anything
it's like
It's not anything. I don't want to hurt anybody or anything. I really
I'm sorry if I did something wrong
Okay, why are you likely assuming you did something wrong? Well, I mean, you know, it's like some people
Maybe I wasn't so nice to some people sometimes. Maybe I don't understand if you're not nice to somebody then
Yeah
It was out of her not of that's where I'm gonna start, you know, it's like it really was
Seriously the bottom of my heart. I love you. That's why I'm still here
And and you're so you're so amazing you're amazing woman
And I hope you I hope you know that, you know, I hope you know that me you've of course. Yes. Yes. Oh, I absolutely do
Yeah, I know everything
I think even
people I've had problems with
There's some there's good and there's good in everyone and Charles Manson even though Charles Manson's parents
I called him no name and
And he was in the he didn't have some fun here. Yeah, he didn't
I'm joking. I don't know
But up to a certain point, I agree with you.
As far as everybody has something nice,
some people really, really don't.
When they look for that one little cheek in your arm.
Where's the hurt?
There's hurt, there's trauma.
There's something there that made them the way they are.
Like that's what I see.
And it's like, and if I dig deep enough,
I will find a little glimmer of light in everybody.
Little a little bit. Maybe it's maybe it's a little bit, but there's like
God the part of God and everybody and I don't want to get religious or like weird
There's a part of God in every single person in this world
There's like a little tiny if it's that one atom of God. There's something
Good in everybody something even
Somebody has out there as a mom that has a fake for someone to be brought in the world, right?
the mother has to
Go through getting her stomach stretched out in nine months of
and then the birth, the pain of birth.
I mean, just imagine this.
Everybody, there's love.
To imagine this, I am a mom.
You know, listen, that's completely wrong though.
You cannot say a mom will be a great mom
just because my mom hated my guts.
So just because you can have the title of mom.
Right.
No.
There's people who are gonna go for it.
We'll brought you in, but just think about.
her stomach got stretched out in nine months,
like you could have had a-
Don't care.
Any mom can have an abortion, right?
And it's not too difficult.
Like any mom can say, I don't want to have a child, right?
I mean, so to bring us into the world,
there is something there, something,
some kind of love, some kind of like-
You can have a brother.
I don't I don't want to be too personal or anything, and I'm sorry if I am but uh, there's something if there's something
I don't want to say I won't say it there's something
There's there's love that brought us into the world. They love brought us into the world somehow, you know, okay?
Let me explain
The situation with me, okay? My mom wanted out of her crazy parents house
So she got with my dad. They had me she hated my guts. You went off to work in the fields
And I didn't get to see that the narcissist that I grew up with totally wrecked my ass.
So, yeah, it's not all sunshine and roses because she had lots of love for my brother.
She had lots of love for my brother.
So I know she was capable.
I just didn't get it.
Right.
nine months. It's a nine month process, right? You know, women don't like usually like their
stomachs stretched out. But still, to keep you alive.
to feed you through her to give birth and giving birth is not a pleasant process either and Erin you know this it's like it's not it's it's it's painful right it's like yeah yeah and so there is something it's okay midnight and I'm talking too much but there's something
and look at all the good you've done to the world.
Look at all the people you've affected.
Like, look at all the beauty you've brought in the world.
Look at how-
I'm working as TV.
I've affected many.
But the the thing about it to psyche is that what I've been told by other female too, especially like
I've seen it like, you know, my wife's seen it with her friends and stuff like that
Like you could sit there and have the title like she said about mom
But some moms don't have that mother instinct. No, it doesn't matter because to give birth
No, I'm sorry, I'm not giving her a pass because
As for being a mother that's a different thing
Then the giving birth part then the giving it was unselfish
That she gave birth to me that would be one thing that she did it for a reason. Okay, and the reason was not me
In that I was kind of like an afterthought. Oh, yeah, I'm gonna have a kid have this understanding you have
But I still say, her stomach got stretched out.
She gave, she had the painful delivery.
And it's like, somewhere in there, there was love.
Somewhere in there.
Somewhere, somewhere in there,
beyond all the selfish reasons,
there was love somewhere in there.
That's what I think, but if I'm wrong.
I'm wrong, but I think the best the best way for anyone to understand is you have to be a female to be able to go through that
Yeah, and that's why I'm not gonna say oh
I'm for abortion or against abortion because it really is up to the the woman, but if you really think about it
women women
To have there's something stressed out like that and they have a painful birth
There has to in the in to nourish the child inside
I'm pretty sure they're not
worried about a couple of
stress marks for, you know, uh,
uh, yeah.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know because I have
what you're saying. I understand.
I know you want to believe that.
I really know that you want to
believe that. That's great. I
don't know. I think it's very
naive, but I'm a man and I
don't have to give birth. I
Ask her how she feels.
Lola.
Lola was like shocked and she's like, what's happening to me?
She's like, I mean, bigger, bigger, bigger.
And then, you know, she was like, what the fuck is happening?
She pushed out five kittens.
You know what she did?
All the five kittens survived.
She loved them.
And it is even though.
Yes.
Point.
Yeah, oh Lola was a great Lola all her kittens survived like that another cat and a kitten or two passed away and that their kittens
their cats birthed but Lola
Lola I bet you listen psyche I bet you if you could talk to Lola
She would say, I hate every single one of you because I'm pregnant and I hate you.
Yeah, but Lola, what do you think about Lola?
Now, it is tricks and she had all her kittens after they got too big.
But Lola, what do you think of him now?
And now?
your friends, right? Look at her. Look at her face.
Of course, yeah, because they're kittens. I mean, they're cats.
Well, like, because, you know, four of her cats, like, left and stuff, but you know what, Triggs chose to stay here, and you know what, another friend, oh, oh, you like that when I, when I rub your ear like that? Like that?
Oh, yeah, the ear, maybe the ear.
I'm gonna get under the cover.
Okay. I don't know if you guys have seen this, but there's a little...
Is he a chimpanzee? I don't know. He's a little monkey and his name is punch. Have you seen anything about this?
Oh, yes with the mother is a fake a fake
Yeah, like a pleasure
And everybody is so fucking mean to him his mom got rid of him didn't want to have anything to do with him
So yeah in nature it does happen. It's not like it's totally unusual
And I'm telling you the whole internet was ready to go to bat for that kid for that baby
I was so mad. I was like how much is a trip to japan?
Well, I'm see I'm not gonna lie like if I could kind of like I mean no one's
You know could ever be the same as yours
But from your experience, I've seen it with my auntie the way she treats my cousins and
She gots her favorite and she gots the one that she hates and she's always been like that like and it's booked up to say that
But it's the honest truth
Yeah, and it does happen. I mean it's not like a a
Weird and unusual thing like even animals or you know, they're gonna say no
I don't want this kid and have nothing to do with it. So what my mom did is
Not really surprising is what I'm trying to say
It's not like it's a one-off thing and never ever happens to anybody but me because I don't want sympathy
I've come to terms with that's who she is my brother's the golden boy
I never was that's fine because I became a really really good person and
That's all I need. It's all matters exactly
Exactly so anyway now that I've done my
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
It's not because I didn't get any, you know, I have that inside me
I don't need somebody to give me that meaning my mom
You know, yeah, she gave birth to me, but that's it. I I came with the love. I got the love from myself
So anyway, I just want you to surround yourself and good people be happy
I'm trying I'm trying and I was gonna say I'm trying to type in chat. There's one thing I can say before I pass out or whatever
There's one thing at like the last word I have is that I love you and that's and it's like
That's one last thing I want to say to anybody is I love you because I had a friend die and stuff
Last thing I said to him was I love you and he said I love you too, you know
It's not a gay thing. It was not anything
That's the last thing we can say to anybody that we love even somebody that we hate
People that we hate maybe we do some or down there
We do love them too, and it's like even the even our haters
I mean, I think it was like music is Marty who did pass away to who was on my show
You know Cyrax at the end of the day was like
I
Mean it's like good thing. You don't know who Syrax is. Yeah, it's a good thing. Don't look at don't look into him
He's he's a he's not a good person, but you know what I want to say
I do love you and I say about five one thing to say. It's like my heart is open to
Anybody and especially and I just want people to do better. I want people to operate more in the spirit of love
That's all I have to say
And shout out to Erin. I think she came up here to let you know that you're not you're that you're not alone, bro
Like y'all might not be going through the same thing, but she kind of somewhat understands
And that's what's up to her and shout out to you
It changes the whole conversation and it's good. It's it's cool. That's cool. See I love you and I love Aaron
Appreciate it. I love my chat and it's like, you know what you guys keep me going you guys
Got good advice for me. You guys have your you know, let's do a damn thing. I said
But if I understand it or not, I still love you.
And that's the bottom of my heart.
If we never talk again or anything,
if I'm gone, whoever is gone, I love you.
And remember that, you remember anything?
Remember that, those three words, I love you.
Man, we're gonna be here for a while, bro.
So don't worry.
We're gonna be here for a while.
Stay here, I don't want to go.
I'm going to skip that. I love you. Don't ever do that thinking. Oh, I can tell him I love him tomorrow
You don't ever skip those don't skip till I love you like like that if it can be the last thing you say to somebody
Because you don't know when someone's gonna be gone. You don't
Very strong as bro
Someone someone that has you know a huge bodybuilder, and I'm very attracted to
They they can be very strong and stuff, but you know a bullet is is stronger than some in a month
And we don't know what will happen to anybody and so if you just remember one thing about me remember that I love you
That's all I want to say
Give me a nice call me and sing it to me
Well, it's been a fucking pleasure I'm gonna go and jump off. Thank you. Thank you. I'm see thank you
Thank you. I wasn't too weird. But you know, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Aaron, I love you. I'm probably going to play a couple of songs. I'm probably passing out soon.
Okay, honey. I've got to go to bed anyway.
Okay. Well, Aaron, Sweet Dreams and May You Be Happy, Fruitful.
May everything go right for you.
I see your dreams coming true.
I see good things happening for you
and you're here for a reason, okay?
And you help people, okay?
Don't forget you help.
I love you, okay?
I love you guys too.
I'll talk to you soon.
Well, let's see.
I mean, I'll see if I can see up any longer, but.
I might be passing out soon, but I'll try to play a couple things for you. Let me see.
I don't know. And I don't put things the best way sometimes, and you know,
Bita, I love you. Cage, I love you. I don't forget that you were like these first people here.
When I was like nobody no one and you were like here. I don't forget that. I love you, and I'm sorry
Things went wrong and self
I'm not perfect. I'm sorry
I'll take the blame. Okay, but at the end of the day I only will have good thoughts about you and
I wish you the best and I'm sorry
I did something wrong. I probably did probably did and I'm not perfect
But you know what you guys are perfect in my eyes and
I'm sorry. I'm sorry things turned out the way they did and forgive me
Yeah, but you're hard to forgive me forgive me
I don't I don't even apology. I just need forgiveness
My heart hurts every night
Thinking about how I messed everything up. I'm sorry
Okay, I'm not trying to be weird or anything. I'm sorry if I messed everything up. I
Love you
If I'm not here tomorrow or whenever I'm not here next week remember
I'm sorry I'm anything from you. I'm just sorry, okay
I'm sorry
I messed up
It was just, just remember it was just me.
I messed up.
I'm sorry.
Here.
Remember this fool, remember this fool.
If I remember gone, remember this fool.
Remember this stupid fool.
That was me. Remember this guy.
And you didn't do anything wrong, I did something wrong. I love you.